<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Obsidian Vault]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>Obsidian Vault</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 13:08:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 13:08:36 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Alyna Cerrine]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Alyna Cerrine In Garden.jpg" src="lib\media\alyna-cerrine-in-garden.jpg"><br>
Lady Alyna Cerrine is the second eldest daughter of the Cellesela House family. As one of the Immortals, she is a controversial figure in the Styx Empire. Her reputation as a lustful noble sometimes harms her and the family as a whole, despite her struggle to control her impulses. Renowned for her skills in herbalism and gardening, her talent in these areas has led her to provide new and sought-after items in the Cellesela Provinces. Her passionate charm is also notable, though it is often overshadowed by her reckless hedonism at night. She always wears silk gloves to protect the skin beneath during her gardening sessions. Her obsession with fleeting passions blinds her to deeper connections. She collects lovers like exotic flowers—admiring them intensely, then forgetting them once the bloom fades. This leaves her isolated, though she’d never admit it.<br>]]></description><link>character\house-of-cellesela\alyna-cerrine.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Cellesela/Alyna Cerrine.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 04:48:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\alyna-cerrine-in-garden.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\alyna-cerrine-in-garden.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cellesela]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Concubine of&nbsp;Croton Alcyon&nbsp;Mother of&nbsp;House Cellesela<img alt="young mother cellesela.gif" src="lib\media\young-mother-cellesela.gif">]]></description><link>character\house-of-cellesela\cellesela.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Cellesela/Cellesela.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 13:08:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\young-mother-cellesela.gif" length="0" type="image/gif"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\young-mother-cellesela.gif&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Creo Ascella]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Creo.jpg" src="lib\media\creo.jpg"><br>Creo Ascella is one of the <a data-href="The Immortals" href="creature\the-immortals.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Immortals</a>, a skilled birdmaster with a talent for taming and caring for even the fiercest and rarest birds. Raised alongside three sisters as the only son, his upbringing influenced the polite and slightly effeminate demeanor of Creo, making him also more approachable and empathetic. He is highly focused on improving his bird-handling techniques and often spends his time observing and interacting with the creatures in his care rather than people. Creo tends to avoid conflicts, preferring quiet environments where he can work undisturbed. He is highly dedicated to his craft and takes great pride in his work, constantly seeking to perfect his technique and build a deeper connection with the birds under his care.<br>**<br>]]></description><link>character\house-of-cellesela\creo-ascella.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Cellesela/Creo Ascella.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 04:30:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\creo.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\creo.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Luna Elysia]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="newluna.png" src="lib\media\newluna.png"><br>Lady Luna Elysia is a quiet and reserved Immortals noble of the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="House of Cellesela" data-href="House of Cellesela" href="house\house-of-cellesela.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">House Cellesela</a>. Despite her introverted personality and the youngest of the siblings, she is known for her exceptional talent in the arts. She is a gifted architect working on many projects for the empire, creating majestic and intricate works of art that are admired by many, and spends much of her time working in isolation. Despite her reserved personality, she is highly sought after by the wealthy and influential members of Styx Empire, who appreciate her skill and attention to detail. Her works are treasured throughout the empire.<br>]]></description><link>character\house-of-cellesela\luna-elysia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Cellesela/Luna Elysia.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:22:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\newluna.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\newluna.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Octavia Vulp]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>**<br><img alt="Young Octavia.jpg" src="lib\media\young-octavia.jpg"><br>Octavia is the eldest sibling and the househead of <a data-href="House Cellesela" href="House Cellesela" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">House Cellesela</a> and its representative in the <a data-href="Styx Empire" href="political-realm\styx-empire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Styx Empire</a>`s court. She has the most experience and for that reason the wisest among the young member of the Family, she can be strict since the family have long lost their parent and have taken parental authority for the siblings. Despite her reputation, however, she was also beloved by the empire populace due to her care in daily livelihood of the common mortals despite her status as <a data-href="The Immortals" href="creature\the-immortals.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Immortals</a>.<br>]]></description><link>character\house-of-cellesela\octavia-vulp.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Cellesela/Octavia Vulp.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:26:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\young-octavia.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\young-octavia.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yeetus Bosimau]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Yeetus Bosimau&nbsp;is a prominent figure in the&nbsp;<a data-href="Styx Empire" href="political-realm\styx-empire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Styx Empire</a>, known for his dealings as a trader of&nbsp;<a data-href="Servus" href="creature\servus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Servus</a>, or slaves. Despite being the younger brother of&nbsp;<a data-href="Zeurgeud Abadi" href="character\house-of-gagon\zeurgeud-abadi.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zeurgeud Abadi</a>], the representative of&nbsp;<a data-href="House of Gagoon" href="house\house-of-gagoon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">House of Gagoon</a> and the richest noble in the empire, Yeetus has carved out a name for himself in a different field. His reputation as a fair and reliable trader of Servus has earned him the trust and respect of many in the empire, and his business dealings have contributed greatly to his wealth and influence. However, rumors persist about the true nature of his business practices, with some suggesting that he may not always be as honest and upstanding as he appears. Regardless, Yeetus continues to thrive in the world of Servus trading, using his cunning and business savvy to navigate the treacherous waters of the&nbsp;<a data-href="Styx Empire" href="political-realm\styx-empire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Styx Empire</a>]'s political and economic landscape.]]></description><link>character\house-of-gagon\yeetus-bosimau.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Gagon/Yeetus Bosimau.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:48:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zeurgeud Abadi]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="zeurkeeur.jpg" src="lib\media\zeurkeeur.jpg"><br>
Zeurgeud Abadi&nbsp;is the older brother of&nbsp;<a data-href="Yeetus Bosimau" href="character\house-of-gagon\yeetus-bosimau.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Yeetus Bosimau</a>&nbsp;and the representative of&nbsp;<a data-href="House Cassio" href="House Cassio" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">House Cassio</a>&nbsp;in the&nbsp;<a data-href="Styx Empire" href="political-realm\styx-empire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Styx Empire</a>. He is the owner of a massive gold mine in the south of the empire, which has made him the richest noble in the Styx Empire. Despite his wealth, Zeurgeud's reputation has changed over time. In the past, he was known for his generosity, but as his wealth grew, he became more greedy and isolated. He no longer interacts with the other nobles in the same way he once did, and many believe that he has become treacherous and cunning in his dealings. Despite this change in personality, Zeurgeud remains one of the most powerful figures in the&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Styx" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Styx" target="_blank">Styx Empire</a>&nbsp;and is respected for his wealth and influence.]]></description><link>character\house-of-gagon\zeurgeud-abadi.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Gagon/Zeurgeud Abadi.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\zeurkeeur.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\zeurkeeur.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Julius Cato]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="JuliusAlt.jpg" src="lib\media\juliusalt.jpg"><br>
Julius, is a noble of House Gaius, known for his cunning and his mastery of strategy. He is a highly skilled commander, with a deep understanding of military tactics and a keen mind for strategy. He is feared by his enemies for his ability to outmaneuver and outwit them, and respected by his allies for his unwavering commitment to victory.<br>Julius is a master of manipulation and deceit, using his wit and his cunning to turn the tide of battle in his favor. He is a calculating and ruthless opponent, always seeking to gain the upper hand and never hesitating to take advantage of any opportunity that presents itself.<br>Together, Samulus and Julius make a formidable team, their combined skills and cunning making them a force to be reckoned with on any battlefield.]]></description><link>character\house-of-gaius\julius-cato.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Gaius/Julius Cato.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\juliusalt.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\juliusalt.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Samulus Marcellus]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Samulus.jpg" src="lib\media\samulus.jpg"><br>Samulus is a noble of House Gaius, known for his discipline and exceptional combat skills. He is a highly trained warrior, with a strong sense of justice and a strict code of honor. He is respected by his peers for his unwavering dedication to his duty, and for his unyielding spirit in the face of adversity.<br>In battle, Samulus is a force to be reckoned with, his skills honed to perfection through years of rigorous training. He wields his weapons with deadly precision, and his enemies tremble at the mere sight of him on the battlefield.<br>Despite his fearsome reputation as a warrior, Samulus is also known for his intelligence and his cunning mind. He is always several steps ahead of his opponents, anticipating their every move and always finding a way to turn the tide of battle in his favor.]]></description><link>character\house-of-gaius\samulus-marcellus.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Gaius/Samulus Marcellus.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:27:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\samulus.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\samulus.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Azullia Ryea]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Lady Azullia Ryea is a skilled and cunning diplomat, known for her charm and ability to win over even the toughest of opponents. She is a member of the prestigious&nbsp;House Rhagaia, and holds a prominent position within the Styx Empire. Despite her friendly demeanor, Azullia is fiercely ambitious and always looking for ways to increase her influence and power. This has put her at odds with her rival,&nbsp;Lady Octavia Vulp&nbsp;of&nbsp;House Cellesela. Despite the rivalry, Azullia is a master of keeping her true intentions hidden, and is feared by many for her cunning and resourcefulness. Despite her sometimes unethical methods, she is widely respected for her ability to get things done and her unwavering determination to succeed.]]></description><link>character\house-of-rhagaia\azullia-ryea.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Rhagaia/Azullia Ryea.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gionni Valen]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Sir Giovanni Galen&nbsp;is the oldest noble in the Styx Empire and a respected leader in both the noble and engineering communities. As a member of House Rhagaia, Sir Giovanni is well known for his contributions to the field of engineering, which have earned him the position of master of the Guild of Engineers. Despite his prestigious standing, Sir Giovanni is known for his philosophical and introspective nature, setting him apart from other nobles in the empire.<br>One of Sir Giovanni's most notable traits is his refusal to use the&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Fountain of Youth" data-href="Fountain of Youth" href="places\fountain-of-youth.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">immortal geyser</a>, or&nbsp;<a data-href="Vitale" href="items\vitale.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow"><span class="iconize-icon-in-link" title="IbBeaker" aria-label="IbBeaker" data-icon="IbBeaker" aria-hidden="true" style="transform: translateY(20%);"><svg width="20px" height="20px" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewBox="0 0 24 24"><path d="M8 3v5.668c0 .415 0 .622-.042.823-.042.202-.124.392-.29.772l-2.235 5.142c-1.098 2.525-1.647 3.788-1.055 4.692C4.97 21 6.348 21 9.1 21h5.798c2.754 0 4.13 0 4.723-.903.592-.904.043-2.167-1.055-4.692l-2.235-5.142c-.166-.38-.248-.57-.29-.772C16 9.29 16 9.083 16 8.668V3m1 11H7M18 3H6" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"></path></svg></span>Vitale</a>, which is commonly consumed by the other nobles in the empire. This stance stems from his deeply held belief that the pursuit of eternal youth and immortality goes against the natural order of life and is at odds with his philosophical views. As a result, Sir Giovanni is often seen as a wise and thoughtful figure, respected for his integrity and unwavering principles.<br>Throughout his life, Sir Giovanni has dedicated himself to his work as an engineer and his pursuit of knowledge, and his contributions have had a lasting impact on the Styx Empire. Despite his age, Sir Giovanni remains as sharp and insightful as ever, and his philosophical and introspective nature continues to set him apart from other nobles in the empire.]]></description><link>character\house-of-rhagaia\gionni-valen.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Rhagaia/Gionni Valen.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Martius Umbra]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Martius Umbra, the talented alchemist noble of House Rhagaia, is known for his innovative and daring approach to alchemy. Despite being the younger brother of&nbsp;Lady Azullia Ryea, Martius is not one to be underestimated. His combination of boldness and intellect makes him a formidable force in the world of alchemy.<br>Martius is confident and ambitious, always eager to push the boundaries of his craft. He is not afraid to take risks, and is always looking for new and innovative solutions to the problems he faces. Martius is a cunning strategist, always several steps ahead of his opponents. He is fiercely intelligent and knows how to use his wits to get what he wants. He is not afraid to use underhanded tactics to achieve his goals, and has a reputation for being a master manipulator. Despite his sometimes shady methods, Martius is respected and feared by many in the alchemical community for his skill and cunning.<br><img alt="Martius.jpg" src="lib\media\martius.jpg">]]></description><link>character\house-of-rhagaia\martius-umbra.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Rhagaia/Martius Umbra.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:27:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\martius.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\martius.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alcyon]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Second King]]></description><link>character\house-of-tyrannite\alcyon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Tyrannite/Alcyon.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ciro Alcyon II]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Nominated Succesor of Alcyon]]></description><link>character\house-of-tyrannite\ciro-alcyon-ii.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Tyrannite/Ciro Alcyon II.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ciro Alycon]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="CiroAlcyon.jpg" src="lib\media\ciroalcyon.jpg"><br>
‎<br>
‎<br>
‎<br>
‎<br>
‎<br>
Emperor Ciro Alcyon, the son of&nbsp;<a data-href="Croton Alcyon" href="character\house-of-tyrannite\croton-alcyon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Croton Alcyon</a>, is a known figure in the Styx Empire. He is a family-oriented man and is said to have a strong bond with his loved ones. He is also known for his gullibility and eccentric nature, which sometimes leads him to impulsive decisions. Despite this, he is widely respected and known as "The Great Builder."<br>Ciro is credited with numerous construction projects that have greatly contributed to the growth and development of the empire. He has a great passion for building and is known to take personal interest in every project he initiates. His dedication to construction has earned him the nickname "The Great Builder."<br>Aside from his love for building, Ciro is also known for his love of adventure. He is often seen traveling to far-off lands, seeking new challenges and experiences. Despite his impulsive nature, he has always managed to come out on top, further cementing his reputation as a fearless and capable leader. With his combination of passion, dedication, and adventurous spirit, Emperor Ciro Alcyon is a true symbol of the Styx Empire's power and might.]]></description><link>character\house-of-tyrannite\ciro-alycon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Tyrannite/Ciro Alycon.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 09:49:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\ciroalcyon.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\ciroalcyon.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Croton Alcyon]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="artwork of Croton.jpg" src="lib\media\artwork-of-croton.jpg">Third King of Styxians<br>Croton alcyon father of alcyon and cellesela line killed by linerian massacre<br>most alcyon line is dissipated on the event leaving ciro more protectful of Potii taygetta]]></description><link>character\house-of-tyrannite\croton-alcyon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Tyrannite/Croton Alcyon.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:14:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\artwork-of-croton.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\artwork-of-croton.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deren Taygetta]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>character\house-of-tyrannite\deren-taygetta.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Tyrannite/Deren Taygetta.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lady Minerva]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="mother minerva.jpg" src="lib\media\mother-minerva.jpg">unknown name]]></description><link>character\house-of-tyrannite\lady-minerva.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Tyrannite/Lady Minerva.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\mother-minerva.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\mother-minerva.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Minerca The First King]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="artwork holyminerca.jpg" src="lib\media\artwork-holyminerca.jpg">First King of Styx]]></description><link>character\house-of-tyrannite\minerca-the-first-king.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Tyrannite/Minerca The First King.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\artwork-holyminerca.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\artwork-holyminerca.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Potii Taygetta]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="noble potii.jpg" src="lib\media\noble-potii.jpg"><br>
Potii Taygetta is a mysterious and unpredictable figure in the Styx Empire's court. With a reputation for being emotionally unstable and cunning, many of the other nobles are wary of his intentions. Despite this, Potii holds a powerful position in the empire as the "Ori," or "royal cleric" to the Imperial Cult religion.<br>This religion is highly revered and respected in the empire, making Potii's role all the more significant. However, many question whether he is truly devoted to the religion, or if he is merely using it as a means to gain power and influence.<br>Potii's eccentric behavior and unpredictable actions only add to the rumors and speculation surrounding him. Some say he is unstable and prone to erratic outbursts, while others believe he is cunning and treacherous. Regardless, Potii Taygetta remains a powerful force to be reckoned with in the Styx Empire, and one that many approach with caution.]]></description><link>character\house-of-tyrannite\potii-taygetta.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Tyrannite/Potii Taygetta.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\noble-potii.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\noble-potii.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Taygetta]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>died captured in first malazaer war with Alcyon]]></description><link>character\house-of-tyrannite\taygetta.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/House of Tyrannite/Taygetta.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Balleon Wensbane]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>serves in Gaius Command on siege of Orbis]]></description><link>character\balleon-wensbane.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/Balleon Wensbane.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Daleth Sehlk]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Daleth Sehlk, one of the Sciatic Immortal nobles and its founding father, is the current governor. His idealistic vision of collaborative nation-states, with commerce as an equalizing opportunity for individuals and new cities to rise, backed by an empire, can rarely be called a utopian future. Yet, it hasn't stopped him from dreaming that his project could be the spark for the collapse of the old order. His naivety, however, is constantly exploited by other nobles, either from the Sciatic League or the Styx Empire, to further their own agendas, often with devastating consequences. His opinion on the aristocracy has made him an outsider among the elite. They tolerate his presence only because the wealth of the League is too valuable to ignore. The public sees him as a polarizing figure, with many lauding him as a champion of opportunity, while others accuse him of protecting the wealthy.]]></description><link>character\daleth-sehlk.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/Daleth Sehlk.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:54:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elara]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Elara.jpg" src="lib\media\elara.jpg"><br>Reverend Sister of <a data-href="Creo Ascella" href="character\house-of-cellesela\creo-ascella.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Creo Ascella</a><br>19yo]]></description><link>character\elara.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/Elara.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 03:07:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\elara.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\elara.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lexius Nexa]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Natives: Leius Necca]]></description><link>character\lexius-nexa.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/Lexius Nexa.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Litmus & Talus]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>character\litmus-&amp;-talus.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/Litmus &amp; Talus.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Malco Vael]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>character\malco-vael.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/Malco Vael.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Semi Lya WIP]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="cover hlarge" src="lib\media\semilya.jpg"><br>
Semi Lya, also known as Xi Li, embodies the qualities of a just and compassionate ruler. She prioritizes the welfare and happiness of her people above personal gain. Known for her humility, she values the opinions and perspectives of her advisors and encourages open dialogue. Her reign is marked by a commitment to justice, equal opportunity, and the preservation of cultural heritage. Semi Lya's unwavering determination to secure independence for her people serves as a beacon of hope and inspiration to those who follow her.]]></description><link>character\semi-lya-wip.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/Semi Lya WIP.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:30:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\semilya.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\semilya.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Taixhu Fenyr]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Natives: Taizu Fai<br>part of Lynx]]></description><link>character\taixhu-fenyr.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/Taixhu Fenyr.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Taneds Akhar]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>leader of tolkhai tribe]]></description><link>character\taneds-akhar.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Character/Taneds Akhar.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chlorolith]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>are constructed being tasked as either a companion of cellesela nobility or specialized worker of important area such as guardian of a dungeon, construction, or even to tend private garden. <br>Chlorolith are made from intricate surgery of humans, commonly a trusted servant with a special plant called Chlorie Roots,<br>
Each fiber of the plants is tied to each muscle to consider the manoeuvrability of its "Pilot", for this reason Chlorolith are hard to encounter to common person and limited its ownership only for house of Cellesela. <br>It appearance differ for each Chlorolith, it all depends on it purpose or the taste of its owner, but they all wear a protective "mask"<br>
or pouch to hide the pilot and a slot for magic incase it require one, this slot for Chartamagica can only be taken of by the owner. <br>Chlorolith are also unable to speak whether its pilot or the body it controls.... ()<br>Known Chloroliths:&nbsp;<a data-href="Litmus &amp; Talus" href="character\litmus-&amp;-talus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Litmus &amp; Talus</a>]]></description><link>creature\chlorolith.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Creature/Chlorolith.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fellarian]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Majestic bird which feather are used in superior arrows, commonly found in Eastern part of Cellesela Dominion the mostly roam the seas consuming fish, only the Cellesela were able to gather feathers of such giant bird, people who tried will often get eaten by it.<br>the procedure of gathering such feather is using drugged substance that would put them to sleep and remove every mature feather from its body, the bird only wakes until its feather will fully grown back while in this deep sleep they were feed by the Birdmaster and released.]]></description><link>creature\fellarian.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Creature/Fellarian.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Servus]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Servus, or enslaved individuals, were an integral part of society in Styx during the medieval period. They were often acquired through various means, including war and debt, and were considered the property of their owners. The temples were among the largest owners of Servus, followed by wealthy individuals and families.<br>The treatment of Servus varied widely depending on their owner, but they generally had very few rights and were forced to perform hard physical labor, often in dangerous conditions. They could be bought, sold, and even killed by their owners. Despite their status, some Servus were able to improve their condition and gain their freedom through various means, such as buying their way out of slavery or earning manumission from their owner.<br>The temples and wealthy families relied heavily on Servus labor to maintain their economic power and social status. The temples owned vast tracts of land and used Servus to work the fields and produce goods, while wealthy families used them as domestic servants and for other manual labor.<br>Overall, the practice of enslaving individuals was a common feature of medieval Styx society and was an important part of the economy and social structure.]]></description><link>creature\servus.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Creature/Servus.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Common Onwixe (unwise)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Common People]]></description><link>creature\the-common-onwixe-(unwise).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Creature/The Common Onwixe (unwise).md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Horned Sea Eagle]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Horned Sea Eagle, a formidable avian predator that commands the skies with its impressive size and striking features. With a wingspan stretching over eight feet, this extraordinary creature possesses a commanding presence in the coastal regions it calls home.<br>The Horned Sea Eagle's most distinctive characteristic is its formidable set of curved, sharp, and metallic-hued horns adorning the crown of its head. These striking horns are not only a testament to its dominance but also serve as powerful tools for defense and capturing prey. As a master of aerial acrobatics, this avian marvel can spot potential meals from great heights, thanks to its exceptional eyesight and keen sense of smell.<br>Equipped with razor-sharp talons that rival the size of a grown human's hand, the Horned Sea Eagle is a fearsome hunter capable of capturing prey much larger than itself. While it primarily feeds on fish and marine creatures, it has been known to exhibit extraordinary hunting prowess by targeting larger land mammals when the opportunity arises.<br>With incredible strength and agility, the Horned Sea Eagle can swoop down from the sky with remarkable speed, grasping its unsuspecting prey with unyielding force. It utilizes its impressive wings to maintain stability during these daring maneuvers, ensuring its targets have little chance of escape. Once caught in its grasp, the Horned Sea Eagle's robust beak, equipped with sharp, hook-like edges, effortlessly tears through the flesh of its prey, allowing it to devour even the most resilient of creatures.<br>While it predominantly seeks aquatic sustenance, the Horned Sea Eagle's reputation for consuming larger land animals has garnered it the awe and respect of those who witness its predatory prowess. Although relatively rare and elusive, the sight of this remarkable bird has become the stuff of legends among coastal communities, often accompanied by tales of epic battles with formidable adversaries such as sheep, cows, and even horses.<br>In the realm of avian predators, the Horned Sea Eagle stands as an apex predator, defying conventional expectations and reminding us of the awe-inspiring diversity found in the animal kingdom. Its ability to capture and consume large land mammals adds to its mythical aura, making it a creature of both reverence and fear.]]></description><link>creature\the-horned-sea-eagle.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Creature/The Horned Sea Eagle.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Immortals]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>some called them the older ones are part people who consumed <a data-href="Vitale" href="items\vitale.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow"><span class="iconize-icon-in-link" title="IbBeaker" aria-label="IbBeaker" data-icon="IbBeaker" aria-hidden="true" style="transform: translateY(20%);"><svg width="20px" height="20px" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewBox="0 0 24 24"><path d="M8 3v5.668c0 .415 0 .622-.042.823-.042.202-.124.392-.29.772l-2.235 5.142c-1.098 2.525-1.647 3.788-1.055 4.692C4.97 21 6.348 21 9.1 21h5.798c2.754 0 4.13 0 4.723-.903.592-.904.043-2.167-1.055-4.692l-2.235-5.142c-.166-.38-.248-.57-.29-.772C16 9.29 16 9.083 16 8.668V3m1 11H7M18 3H6" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"></path></svg></span>Vitale</a> compared to <a data-href="The Common Onwixe (unwise)" href="creature\the-common-onwixe-(unwise).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Common Onwixe (unwise)</a> who born without]]></description><link>creature\the-immortals.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Creature/The Immortals.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Walking Samurai]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Walking Samurai is a folk story of Samurai Armor without the body guarding the region with Katana]]></description><link>creature\the-walking-samurai.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Creature/The Walking Samurai.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alexians Culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>culture\alexians-culture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Culture/Alexians Culture.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Daxos Culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Located in the Zeurkeur Province<br>The Daxos, people of the high mountain<br>
Influenced both by Styxian and Tora influences, thrives as a diligent and industrious society. the people of Daxos have built their reputation around mining, ore extraction, blacksmithing, pottery, and sculpture.<br>within the ashlands, a volcanic crater region, Daxos is surrounded by a rugged and awe-inspiring landscape. The people have ingeniously sculpted their buildings into the cliffs, utilizing the very stones they extract from the earth. This architectural technique integrates their structures with the natural surroundings.<br>In Daxos, social hierarchy is visually apparent. The height level and elaborate decoration of the buildings serve as indicators of one's status. The noble class resides at the pinnacle of the cliffs, their residences lavishly adorned with terracotta decorations that reflect their wealth and influence.<br>On the other hand, the commoners toil in the mines below, extracting the valuable resources that fuel Daxos' economy. Their modest dwellings dot the lower regions, symbolizing their hard work and dedication to the prosperity of the culture.<br>The people of Daxos take great pride in their craftsmanship, evident in their meticulously crafted pottery and intricate sculptures. The artisans of Daxos are revered for their ability to transform raw materials into works of art, showcasing the culture's creative spirit.<br>The volcanic ashlands surrounding Daxos not only provide fertile ground for mining but also imbue the region with a distinct atmosphere. The presence of volcanic activity lends an air of mystique and resilience to the culture, shaping their resilience and determination.<br>Daxos, the convergence of Styxian and Tora traditions, has forged a society rooted in hard work, skilled craftsmanship, and a clear social hierarchy. Its unique architectural style, resource-rich mines, and volcanic surroundings make it a distinctive and captivating culture within the realm.]]></description><link>culture\daxos-culture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Culture/Daxos Culture.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elvish Culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Mixeed<br>Capopy<br>Leafen]]></description><link>culture\elvish-culture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Culture/Elvish Culture.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Incazil Culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>known for its night time schedule the incanzil are also known for its high literacy rate since they are used to exchange knowledge with the Exiled Malazaer Kingdom<br>they are located in Dominion of Rhagaia<br>based on joseon and mesoamerican culture]]></description><link>culture\incazil-culture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Culture/Incazil Culture.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Linerian Culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>located in Lynx/Lineria]]></description><link>culture\linerian-culture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Culture/Linerian Culture.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Polysia Culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Polysia<br>
located within the realm of the Cellesela Dominion<br>In the western expanse of the Cellesela Province, the Polysia-Estuarin people have a rich heritage that showcases their mastery of intricate pagodas, majestic stupas, and stone totems. the Polysia-Estuarin reveres their deceased by laying them to rest within the central courtyard, adorned with stone platforms and elaborately carved statues. This sacred space pays homage to their ancestors, embodying a profound connection to the past and the wisdom they impart.<br>Conversely, in the eastern reaches characterized by vast swamplands, the Polysia-Riparian people exhibit their resourcefulness by constructing dwellings from timber and thatch instead of stone foundation. Native hardwoods, meticulously selected for their strength, form the foundation and support structures, while roofs woven from dried leaves and grasses provide insulation and shelter from the elements. built atop wooden foundations, harmoniously coexist with the ever-changing swampy environment, Signifying utmost reverence for the departed, a unique tradition unfolds as the deceased are placed upon ceremonial canoes, which are then set ablaze in a poignant fire dance. This powerful ritual symbolizes a spiritual journey into realms beyond mortal existence. (AI)<br>Variant: East/Swamp: Riparian and West/Seas: Estuarin]]></description><link>culture\polysia-culture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Culture/Polysia Culture.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sciatic Culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>culture\sciatic-culture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Culture/Sciatic Culture.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Song Culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>located in northern province of Lineria (Lynx)<br>based on chinese culture]]></description><link>culture\song-culture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Culture/Song Culture.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Styx Culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Mesopotamia ]]></description><link>culture\styx-culture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Culture/Styx Culture.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tolkhai Culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>located in Dominion of Gaius<br>based on turkic culture<br>nomadic group which subjugated by Styx Empire through Gaius <br>lead by <a data-href="Taneds Akhar" href="character\taneds-akhar.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Taneds Akhar</a><br>Descendants of the Ancients]]></description><link>culture\tolkhai-culture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Culture/Tolkhai Culture.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tora Culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>located in Caossi Dominion the native culture of the region<br>based on ancient egptian and mali/songhai empire?]]></description><link>culture\tora-culture.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Culture/Tora Culture.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Styx-Lineria War]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Styx-Lineria War was a conflict between the tribes of the Styx and the Lineria Kingdom in the early history of the region. The war began when the Linerians, seeking to expand their territory, launched a series of attacks against the Styx tribes.<br>Initially, the Styx tribes were caught off guard and suffered heavy losses. However, they were able to rally under the leadership of Minerca, an elder of the tribes, and began to fight back against the Linerians.<br>The Linerians, already weakened by internal strife and disease, were unable to withstand the fierce resistance of the Styx tribes. The Styx won battle after battle, slowly pushing the Linerians back and claiming siege to their kingdom.<br>One key factor in the Styx tribes' success was the weakness of the Linerians. The Linerians were beset by infighting and illness, which greatly reduced their ability to fight effectively. Meanwhile, the Styx tribes, though initially caught off guard, were able to adapt to the changing conditions of the war and develop effective tactics and strategies to counter the Linerians' advances.<br>As a result of their victory, the Styx tribes were able to claim the Linerian kingdom as their own and slowly adapted to urban life, ushering in a new era of prosperity for the region]]></description><link>events\styx-lineria-war.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Events/Styx-Lineria War.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Guild of Rhagaia]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Alchemica Guild leaded by Atomic <br>the guild does not believe life and death need one another, <br>death is a mistake of the other not the other<br>the belief happens since the ascend of immortality conflicting this view with the native belief where life &amp; death are equal]]></description><link>factions\guild-of-rhagaia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Guild of Rhagaia.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Mothers]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>The Mother is a notorious bounty hunter group operating in the shadows of society. Their nefarious activities revolve around the kidnapping of children from their families, with the intention of selling them to the immortal nobility as adopted heirs. However, their brutal selection process is far from fair. Children who do not meet their stringent criteria or fail to impress the immortals are condemned to a life of slavery, while the chosen ones are sent to the prestigious School for Immortal Heir, where they undergo intensive training.<br>The Mother's operations fear into the hearts of either poor or rich parents alike across the land, as they brazenly snatch children from their homes under the cover of darkness. The group is shrouded in utmost secrecy, their true identities hidden behind masks and aliases. They employ a network of paid operatives and trackers, enabling them to locate and capture their targets with ruthless efficiency.<br>In the cruel world orchestrated by The Mother, children are reduced to commodities, mere objects to be bought and sold. Those deemed worthy of the immortal nobility are given a chance at a privileged life. At the School for Immortal Heir, they are subjected to rigorous training in etiquette, combat, and other forms of arts, preparing them to assume positions of power and influence in the immortal realm.<br>The Mother's dark deeds have not gone unnoticed, and whispers of their exploits permeate the criminal underworld. Their actions have attracted the attention of rebel factions and concerned citizens, who strive to expose and dismantle their vile operations.<br>]]></description><link>factions\the-mothers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/The Mothers.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:16:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ori]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="the Ori priest.jpg" src="lib\media\the-ori-priest.jpg"><br>
Also known as The Father]]></description><link>factions\the-ori.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/The Ori.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\the-ori-priest.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\the-ori-priest.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[House of Cellesela]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Cellesela Banner 1.png" src="lib\media\cellesela-banner-1.png">The House of Cellesela&nbsp;was one of the most renowned houses in the Styx Empire, renowned for their beautiful gardens, stunning architecture, and their skill in falconry. The House of Cellesela was known for their use of a goose-like bird native to their Cellesela lands, and their use of the birds' feathers to create the most effective arrows in the Styx Empire. This made the House of Cellesela renowned for their archers, and their mastery of the bow was feared and respected by all who heard of it.<br>Creo Ascella was proud to be a part of this powerful and respected house, and he was determined to uphold the family name and the traditions of the House of Cellesela. Unlike his sister Octavia, who was known as a skilled archer and a fierce warrior, Creo was known for his ability to tame the birds used for falconry. He had a gentle touch and a way with the creatures that made him one of the most skilled falconers in the Styx Empire.<br>Luna Elysia was renowned for her knowledge of plants and her ability to cultivate the most beautiful gardens in the Styx Empire, while Alyna Cerrine was known for her artistry and her skill in creating stunning architecture. Together, the four siblings of the House of Stella were a powerful and influential family, respected by all who knew of them.<br>The House of Cellesela was a symbol of strength, beauty, and tradition in the Styx Empire, and Noble Creo Ascella was proud to be a part of it. With his gentle touch and his way with the birds, he was ready to continue the family's traditions and lead them to glory.<br>Knowledge

“Image.png” could not be found.  


<br><br><br>Octavia Vulp<br><br>**<br><img alt="Young Octavia.jpg" src="lib\media\young-octavia.jpg"><br>Octavia is the eldest sibling and the househead of <a data-href="House Cellesela" href="House Cellesela" class="internal-link is-unresolved" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">House Cellesela</a> and its representative in the <a data-href="Styx Empire" href="political-realm\styx-empire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Styx Empire</a>`s court. She has the most experience and for that reason the wisest among the young member of the Family, she can be strict since the family have long lost their parent and have taken parental authority for the siblings. Despite her reputation, however, she was also beloved by the empire populace due to her care in daily livelihood of the common mortals despite her status as <a data-href="The Immortals" href="creature\the-immortals.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Immortals</a>.<br><br>
Alyna Cerrine<br><br><img alt="Alyna Cerrine In Garden.jpg" src="lib\media\alyna-cerrine-in-garden.jpg"><br>
Lady Alyna Cerrine is the second eldest daughter of the Cellesela House family. As one of the Immortals, she is a controversial figure in the Styx Empire. Her reputation as a lustful noble sometimes harms her and the family as a whole, despite her struggle to control her impulses. Renowned for her skills in herbalism and gardening, her talent in these areas has led her to provide new and sought-after items in the Cellesela Provinces. Her passionate charm is also notable, though it is often overshadowed by her reckless hedonism at night. She always wears silk gloves to protect the skin beneath during her gardening sessions. Her obsession with fleeting passions blinds her to deeper connections. She collects lovers like exotic flowers—admiring them intensely, then forgetting them once the bloom fades. This leaves her isolated, though she’d never admit it.<br><br>
Creo Ascella<br><br>
  
  
  
<img class="banner-image full-width draggable" draggable="false" src="lib\media\1676564327502.jpg" style="object-position: 50% 56.806%;"><br><img alt="Creo.jpg" src="lib\media\creo.jpg"><br>Creo Ascella is one of the <a data-href="The Immortals" href="creature\the-immortals.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Immortals</a>, a skilled birdmaster with a talent for taming and caring for even the fiercest and rarest birds. Raised alongside three sisters as the only son, his upbringing influenced the polite and slightly effeminate demeanor of Creo, making him also more approachable and empathetic. He is highly focused on improving his bird-handling techniques and often spends his time observing and interacting with the creatures in his care rather than people. Creo tends to avoid conflicts, preferring quiet environments where he can work undisturbed. He is highly dedicated to his craft and takes great pride in his work, constantly seeking to perfect his technique and build a deeper connection with the birds under his care.<br>**<br><br>
Luna Elysia<br><br>
  
  
  
<img class="banner-image full-width draggable" draggable="false" src="lib\media\newluna.png" style="object-position: 50% 36.29%;"><br><img alt="newluna.png" src="lib\media\newluna.png"><br>Lady Luna Elysia is a quiet and reserved Immortals noble of the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="House of Cellesela" data-href="House of Cellesela" href="house\house-of-cellesela.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">House Cellesela</a>. Despite her introverted personality and the youngest of the siblings, she is known for her exceptional talent in the arts. She is a gifted architect working on many projects for the empire, creating majestic and intricate works of art that are admired by many, and spends much of her time working in isolation. Despite her reserved personality, she is highly sought after by the wealthy and influential members of Styx Empire, who appreciate her skill and attention to detail. Her works are treasured throughout the empire.<br><br>
Cellesela<br><br><br>Concubine of&nbsp;Croton Alcyon&nbsp;Mother of&nbsp;House Cellesela<img alt="young mother cellesela.gif" src="lib\media\young-mother-cellesela.gif">]]></description><link>house\house-of-cellesela.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">House/House of Cellesela.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\cellesela-banner-1.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\cellesela-banner-1.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[House of Gagoon]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Cassio Emblem.png" src="lib\media\cassio-emblem.png">House of Cassio&nbsp;is one of the most powerful noble houses in the Styx Empire. With Zeurkur Aproxima as its current representative, House Cassio is known for its vast wealth and resources. Situated in the southern part of the main continent "Continenta", House Cassio holds a staggering 80% of the Empire's gold and ore supplies, making them the largest supplier of these valuable resources. The immense wealth and power of House Cassio has made them a force to be reckoned with, and their influence in the Empire's political and economic landscape is undeniable. Despite its current representative, Zeurkur Aproxima, becoming increasingly greedy and isolated over time, the house remains a force to be reckoned with.<br>In addition to their wealth and power, House Cassio is also known for its trading practices, especially in the area of Servus, or contract servants. Yeetus Boximau, the younger brother of Zeurkur, is a well-known trader of Servus and is known for his expertise in this area. House Cassio is therefore a major player in the Servus trade, which is a significant source of income for the empire.<br>Overall, House Cassio is a respected and influential noble house in the Styx Empire, known for its wealth, power, and business acumen. Despite the eccentricities and greed of its current representative, Zeurkur, House Cassio continues to play a key role in the affairs of the empire.<br><br><br>Zeurgeud Abadi<br><br><img alt="zeurkeeur.jpg" src="lib\media\zeurkeeur.jpg"><br>
Zeurgeud Abadi&nbsp;is the older brother of&nbsp;<a data-href="Yeetus Bosimau" href="character\house-of-gagon\yeetus-bosimau.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Yeetus Bosimau</a>&nbsp;and the representative of&nbsp;<a data-href="House Cassio" href="House Cassio" class="internal-link is-unresolved" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">House Cassio</a>&nbsp;in the&nbsp;<a data-href="Styx Empire" href="political-realm\styx-empire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Styx Empire</a>. He is the owner of a massive gold mine in the south of the empire, which has made him the richest noble in the Styx Empire. Despite his wealth, Zeurgeud's reputation has changed over time. In the past, he was known for his generosity, but as his wealth grew, he became more greedy and isolated. He no longer interacts with the other nobles in the same way he once did, and many believe that he has become treacherous and cunning in his dealings. Despite this change in personality, Zeurgeud remains one of the most powerful figures in the&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Styx" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Styx" target="_blank">Styx Empire</a>&nbsp;and is respected for his wealth and influence.<br>
Yeetus Bosimau<br><br>Yeetus Bosimau&nbsp;is a prominent figure in the&nbsp;<a data-href="Styx Empire" href="political-realm\styx-empire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Styx Empire</a>, known for his dealings as a trader of&nbsp;<a data-href="Servus" href="creature\servus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Servus</a>, or slaves. Despite being the younger brother of&nbsp;<a data-href="Zeurgeud Abadi" href="character\house-of-gagon\zeurgeud-abadi.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zeurgeud Abadi</a>], the representative of&nbsp;<a data-href="House of Gagoon" href="house\house-of-gagoon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">House of Gagoon</a> and the richest noble in the empire, Yeetus has carved out a name for himself in a different field. His reputation as a fair and reliable trader of Servus has earned him the trust and respect of many in the empire, and his business dealings have contributed greatly to his wealth and influence. However, rumors persist about the true nature of his business practices, with some suggesting that he may not always be as honest and upstanding as he appears. Regardless, Yeetus continues to thrive in the world of Servus trading, using his cunning and business savvy to navigate the treacherous waters of the&nbsp;<a data-href="Styx Empire" href="political-realm\styx-empire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Styx Empire</a>]'s political and economic landscape.]]></description><link>house\house-of-gagoon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">House/House of Gagoon.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:48:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\cassio-emblem.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\cassio-emblem.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[House of Gaius]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The House of Gaius&nbsp;is renowned throughout the Styx Empire for its Majestic Mount Stables, which are home to some of the strongest and most magnificent steeds in the land. The stables are a symbol of the House's military might, and the Gaius family's long-standing tradition of breeding and training powerful heavy cavalry units. The horses raised in the stables are prized not only for their strength and speed, but also for their beauty and grace, making them highly sought after by other noble houses and military organizations throughout the empire.<br>The House of Gaius is also known for its militaristic culture, with a strong emphasis on discipline, combat training, and martial prowess. Members of the House are raised to be warriors and leaders, and they are expected to excel in both physical and strategic warfare. The House of Gaius is respected and feared by many of its vassals and neighbors, and it is known for its fierce loyalty to the Styx Empire and its unwavering commitment to maintaining the safety and security of its lands and people. With its powerful cavalry, skilled warriors, and military expertise, House Gaius is a formidable force in the Styx Empire, and it is widely regarded as one of the greatest and most influential houses in the land.<br>The emblem of House of Gaius features a majestic horse rearing up on its hind legs, with its mane and tail flowing in the wind. The horse is surrounded by a circle of gold, which symbolizes the wealth and power of the House. The background is a deep blue, representing the loyalty and bravery of the Gaius family. The emblem is often displayed on the shields and banners of House Gaius's heavy cavalry units, as well as on the walls of its castles and fortresses.<br><br>Samulus Marcellus<br><br><img alt="Samulus.jpg" src="lib\media\samulus.jpg"><br>Samulus is a noble of House Gaius, known for his discipline and exceptional combat skills. He is a highly trained warrior, with a strong sense of justice and a strict code of honor. He is respected by his peers for his unwavering dedication to his duty, and for his unyielding spirit in the face of adversity.<br>In battle, Samulus is a force to be reckoned with, his skills honed to perfection through years of rigorous training. He wields his weapons with deadly precision, and his enemies tremble at the mere sight of him on the battlefield.<br>Despite his fearsome reputation as a warrior, Samulus is also known for his intelligence and his cunning mind. He is always several steps ahead of his opponents, anticipating their every move and always finding a way to turn the tide of battle in his favor.<br>
Julius Cato<br><br><img alt="JuliusAlt.jpg" src="lib\media\juliusalt.jpg"><br>
Julius, is a noble of House Gaius, known for his cunning and his mastery of strategy. He is a highly skilled commander, with a deep understanding of military tactics and a keen mind for strategy. He is feared by his enemies for his ability to outmaneuver and outwit them, and respected by his allies for his unwavering commitment to victory.<br>Julius is a master of manipulation and deceit, using his wit and his cunning to turn the tide of battle in his favor. He is a calculating and ruthless opponent, always seeking to gain the upper hand and never hesitating to take advantage of any opportunity that presents itself.<br>Together, Samulus and Julius make a formidable team, their combined skills and cunning making them a force to be reckoned with on any battlefield.]]></description><link>house\house-of-gaius.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">House/House of Gaius.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\samulus.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\samulus.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[House of Rhagaia]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Rhagaia Emblem 1.png" src="lib\media\rhagaia-emblem-1.png">House of Rhagaia&nbsp;is known throughout the Styx Empire as a bastion of wisdom and knowledge. This is due to the vast Grand Library that is sponsored and funded heavily by the Rhagaia nobles. This investment has attracted many of the brightest scholars and researchers to the House, making it the source of knowledge and learning in the entire empire. The Grand Library houses countless books, manuscripts, and scrolls, many of which are ancient texts of great value and rarity. The Rhagaia nobles, who take great pride in their House's reputation for learning, are always eager to support new and groundbreaking research. They are known for their philosophical and introspective nature, and are respected throughout the empire for their wisdom and understanding. With its vast wealth of knowledge and its strong commitment to learning, House of Rhagaia is truly a force to be reckoned with in the Styx Empire.<br>Knowledge

“Image.png” could not be found.  


<br><br><br>Azullia Ryea<br><br>Lady Azullia Ryea is a skilled and cunning diplomat, known for her charm and ability to win over even the toughest of opponents. She is a member of the prestigious&nbsp;House Rhagaia, and holds a prominent position within the Styx Empire. Despite her friendly demeanor, Azullia is fiercely ambitious and always looking for ways to increase her influence and power. This has put her at odds with her rival,&nbsp;Lady Octavia Vulp&nbsp;of&nbsp;House Cellesela. Despite the rivalry, Azullia is a master of keeping her true intentions hidden, and is feared by many for her cunning and resourcefulness. Despite her sometimes unethical methods, she is widely respected for her ability to get things done and her unwavering determination to succeed.<br>
Martius Umbra<br><br>
  
  
  
<img class="banner-image full-width draggable" draggable="false" src="lib\media\martius2.jpg" style="object-position: 50% 34%;"><br>Martius Umbra, the talented alchemist noble of House Rhagaia, is known for his innovative and daring approach to alchemy. Despite being the younger brother of&nbsp;Lady Azullia Ryea, Martius is not one to be underestimated. His combination of boldness and intellect makes him a formidable force in the world of alchemy.<br>Martius is confident and ambitious, always eager to push the boundaries of his craft. He is not afraid to take risks, and is always looking for new and innovative solutions to the problems he faces. Martius is a cunning strategist, always several steps ahead of his opponents. He is fiercely intelligent and knows how to use his wits to get what he wants. He is not afraid to use underhanded tactics to achieve his goals, and has a reputation for being a master manipulator. Despite his sometimes shady methods, Martius is respected and feared by many in the alchemical community for his skill and cunning.<br><img alt="Martius.jpg" src="lib\media\martius.jpg"><br>
Gionni Valen<br><br>Sir Giovanni Galen&nbsp;is the oldest noble in the Styx Empire and a respected leader in both the noble and engineering communities. As a member of House Rhagaia, Sir Giovanni is well known for his contributions to the field of engineering, which have earned him the position of master of the Guild of Engineers. Despite his prestigious standing, Sir Giovanni is known for his philosophical and introspective nature, setting him apart from other nobles in the empire.<br>One of Sir Giovanni's most notable traits is his refusal to use the&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Fountain of Youth" data-href="Fountain of Youth" href="places\fountain-of-youth.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">immortal geyser</a>, or&nbsp;<a data-href="Vitale" href="items\vitale.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow"><span class="iconize-icon-in-link" title="IbBeaker" aria-label="IbBeaker" data-icon="IbBeaker" aria-hidden="true" style="transform: translateY(20%);"><svg width="20px" height="20px" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewBox="0 0 24 24"><path d="M8 3v5.668c0 .415 0 .622-.042.823-.042.202-.124.392-.29.772l-2.235 5.142c-1.098 2.525-1.647 3.788-1.055 4.692C4.97 21 6.348 21 9.1 21h5.798c2.754 0 4.13 0 4.723-.903.592-.904.043-2.167-1.055-4.692l-2.235-5.142c-.166-.38-.248-.57-.29-.772C16 9.29 16 9.083 16 8.668V3m1 11H7M18 3H6" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"></path></svg></span>Vitale</a>, which is commonly consumed by the other nobles in the empire. This stance stems from his deeply held belief that the pursuit of eternal youth and immortality goes against the natural order of life and is at odds with his philosophical views. As a result, Sir Giovanni is often seen as a wise and thoughtful figure, respected for his integrity and unwavering principles.<br>Throughout his life, Sir Giovanni has dedicated himself to his work as an engineer and his pursuit of knowledge, and his contributions have had a lasting impact on the Styx Empire. Despite his age, Sir Giovanni remains as sharp and insightful as ever, and his philosophical and introspective nature continues to set him apart from other nobles in the empire.]]></description><link>house\house-of-rhagaia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">House/House of Rhagaia.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:09:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\rhagaia-emblem-1.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\rhagaia-emblem-1.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Royal House of Tyrannite]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>The Royal House of Tyrannite, formerly known as the Trianite Dynasty, is the reigning noble house in the Styx Empire, with Ciro Alcyon as its current leader, succeeding Croton Alycon. This house is known for its exceptional power and influence within the Empire, with many notable members including Potii Taygetta and Nizar Eesa. The Royal House of Tyrannite holds significant political and military power, and is responsible for maintaining the stability and prosperity of the Empire. What sets the Royal House of Tyrannite apart from other noble houses is its hold of "Vitale," a mysterious gas that is said to grant immortality. Over the years, the Royal House of Tyrannite has established itself as a symbol of strength, honor, and tradition, and is deeply respected by the people of the Styx Empire.<br><br><br>Ciro Alycon<br><br><img alt="CiroAlcyon.jpg" src="lib\media\ciroalcyon.jpg"><br>
‎<br>
‎<br>
‎<br>
‎<br>
‎<br>
Emperor Ciro Alcyon, the son of&nbsp;<a data-href="Croton Alcyon" href="character\house-of-tyrannite\croton-alcyon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Croton Alcyon</a>, is a known figure in the Styx Empire. He is a family-oriented man and is said to have a strong bond with his loved ones. He is also known for his gullibility and eccentric nature, which sometimes leads him to impulsive decisions. Despite this, he is widely respected and known as "The Great Builder."<br>Ciro is credited with numerous construction projects that have greatly contributed to the growth and development of the empire. He has a great passion for building and is known to take personal interest in every project he initiates. His dedication to construction has earned him the nickname "The Great Builder."<br>Aside from his love for building, Ciro is also known for his love of adventure. He is often seen traveling to far-off lands, seeking new challenges and experiences. Despite his impulsive nature, he has always managed to come out on top, further cementing his reputation as a fearless and capable leader. With his combination of passion, dedication, and adventurous spirit, Emperor Ciro Alcyon is a true symbol of the Styx Empire's power and might.]<br>Potii Taygetta<br><br><img alt="noble potii.jpg" src="lib\media\noble-potii.jpg"><br>
Potii Taygetta is a mysterious and unpredictable figure in the Styx Empire's court. With a reputation for being emotionally unstable and cunning, many of the other nobles are wary of his intentions. Despite this, Potii holds a powerful position in the empire as the "Ori," or "royal cleric" to the Imperial Cult religion.<br>This religion is highly revered and respected in the empire, making Potii's role all the more significant. However, many question whether he is truly devoted to the religion, or if he is merely using it as a means to gain power and influence.<br>Potii's eccentric behavior and unpredictable actions only add to the rumors and speculation surrounding him. Some say he is unstable and prone to erratic outbursts, while others believe he is cunning and treacherous. Regardless, Potii Taygetta remains a powerful force to be reckoned with in the Styx Empire, and one that many approach with caution.<br>
Ciro Alcyon II<br><br>Nominated Succesor of Alcyon<br>
Minerca The First King<br><br><img alt="artwork holyminerca.jpg" src="lib\media\artwork-holyminerca.jpg">First King of Styx<br>
Lady Minerva<br><br><img alt="mother minerva.jpg" src="lib\media\mother-minerva.jpg">unknown name]]></description><link>house\royal-house-of-tyrannite.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">House/Royal House of Tyrannite.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:20:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\ciroalcyon.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\ciroalcyon.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dragon Silk]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="dragonspider.png" src="lib\media\dragonspider.png">In the opulent realm of Continenta, where extravagance and grandeur reign supreme, there exists a fabric of unparalleled allure known as Dragon Silk. Crafted from the elusive and delicate threads spun by ancient spiders, this remarkable textile possesses a mesmerizing beauty that captivates all who behold it.<br>Dragon Silk is meticulously handwoven by skilled artisans who delicately extract the ethereal strands from the rarest species of enchanted spiders. Each intricate thread, shimmering with a lustrous iridescence, is as fine as a whisper and yet stronger than the noblest steel.<br>Known for its exquisite rarity, Dragon Silk is a prized possession of the wealthiest nobles, an emblem of their opulence and status.<br>But it is not only its aesthetic splendor that distinguishes Dragon Silk. Those adorned in garments woven from this magical fabric are said to be bestowed with a remarkable resilience. The strands of Dragon Silk possess an inherent protection, rendering the wearer impervious to the bite of a common sword. As blades clash against its ethereal sheen, they recoil in futile resistance.<br>But there is more to Dragon Silk's mystique. The touch of this extraordinary fabric upon the skin holds the power of rejuvenation. it is rumored that the whispers of healing magic are interwoven within the fabric itself.<br>However, obtaining even a sliver of Dragon Silk is a quest reserved for the fortunate few who possess both immense wealth and insurmountable influence. Its rarity and the arduous process of its creation render it a treasure unattainable by all but the highest echelons of society.]]></description><link>items\dragon-silk.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Items/Dragon Silk.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\dragonspider.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\dragonspider.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vitale]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="OldBuilding.jpg" src="lib\media\oldbuilding.jpg"><br>
Vitale&nbsp;is a byproduct of the&nbsp;<a data-href="Fountain of Youth" href="places\fountain-of-youth.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Fountain of Youth</a>, created as a result of the Styx Empire's efforts to regulate the consumption of the Fountain. It is essentially a concentrated form of the water from the geyser, containing a high concentration of helium and other unknown substances that give it its youth-restoring properties.<br>Vitale is highly sought after, both by the nobility of the Styx Empire and by those who wish to extend their own lives. The Styx Empire has a monopoly on the production and distribution of Vitale, which they use to maintain the loyalty of their vassals and to increase their own wealth.<br>Despite its high price, Vitale is still in high demand due to its ability to extend life and keep its users youthful and vital. The obsession with immortality that led to the creation of Vitale continues to drive its popularity, with many people willing to pay any price for a chance to live forever.<br>However, Vitale is not without its dangers. The overconsumption of Vitale can result in serious side effects, including infertility. Despite this knowledge, the nobles of the Styx Empire continue to consume Vitale, driven by their desire for eternal youth and vitality.]]></description><link>items\vitale.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Items/Vitale.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\oldbuilding.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\oldbuilding.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Laufar]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\cassio-region\laufar.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Cassio Region/Laufar.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mineralia Magna]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="MineraliaMagna.png" src="lib\media\mineraliamagna.png">Mineralia Magna, the slave capital city of the Dominion of Cassio, stands as a testament to the oppressive rule and extensive mining operations of the region. Situated between the treacherous ashlands and surrounded by volatile volcanic and geothermal activity, the city thrives on the back of an elaborate supply network that encompasses intricate tunnels and well-maintained roads.<br>The heart of Mineralia Magna lies in its expansive mines, where countless slaves toil under harsh conditions to extract valuable minerals and resources. The city's wealth and power are derived from the fruits of their labor, fueling the Dominion's dominance in trade and industry.<br>Carved into the very cliffs that yield its stone, Mineralia Magna's architecture is a marvel of ingenuity and adaptability. Buildings emerge seamlessly from the rugged rock faces, sculpted by skilled hands that have harnessed the very essence of the earth. Each structure, a testament to the indomitable spirit of those who toil within these unforgiving lands.<br>A palpable sense of hierarchy emanates from the city's striking skyline. The noble class occupies the lofty heights, their residences perched atop the cliffs, overlooking the domain they rule. These opulent dwellings stand as proud symbols of wealth and power, adorned with intricate terracotta decorations that catch the light and proclaim their status to all who behold them.<br>Far below, in the depths of the city, lies a different world. The commoners, condemned to a life of labor and servitude, dwell in the shadow of their noble counterparts. Their humble abodes, devoid of elaborate ornamentation, stand as stark reminders of their place in this rigid social order.<br>Despite its brutal nature, Mineralia Magna boasts a remarkably efficient supply network. Underneath the city, there is an intricate network of tunnels that intersect, providing a convenient means of transporting goods and resources. On the surface, efficiently built roads enable the smooth movement of supplies into and out of the city, ensuring a constant flow of wealth.<br>The precarious positioning of Mineralia Magna between the ashlands and the volatile volcanic and geothermal zones adds an element of danger to daily life. The constant threat of volcanic eruptions and other geothermal disturbances serves as a reminder of the unforgiving nature of the environment in which the city thrives.<br>In this slave capital city, the oppressive rule of the Dominion of Cassio is palpable. Mineralia Magna's extensive mines, intricate supply network, and the constant juxtaposition between the perilous ashlands and volcanic activity paint a stark picture of the harsh realities endured by both slaves and those who profit from their labor.]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\cassio-region\mineralia-magna.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Cassio Region/Mineralia Magna.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\mineraliamagna.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\mineraliamagna.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Servs Landing]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>City of slaves trading port in a wikipedia style for fictional writing]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\cassio-region\servs-landing.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Cassio Region/Servs Landing.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cabantha]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\cellesela-region\cabantha.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Cellesela Region/Cabantha.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hyperia]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Capital Dominion of Cellesela]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\cellesela-region\hyperia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Cellesela Region/Hyperia.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hyrios]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\cellesela-region\hyrios.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Cellesela Region/Hyrios.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nimrod]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\cellesela-region\nimrod.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Cellesela Region/Nimrod.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Selene]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\cellesela-region\selene.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Cellesela Region/Selene.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Seos]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Seos, situated at the heart of the Styx Empire, is a thriving city renowned for its agricultural prowess. Governed by the enigmatic Lady Alyna Cerrine, Seos has earned its reputation as the empire's breadbasket and a haven of natural beauty.<br><br>Seos is blessed with vast, fertile plains stretching as far as the eye can see. These fertile lands have allowed the city to flourish as an agricultural hub. Golden wheat fields, lush vineyards, and orchards heavy with fruit dominate the landscape, providing a constant food supply for the empire.<br><br>One of Seos' defining features is its stunning gardens. Governed by Lady Alyna Cerrine, an adept herbalist and gardener, these green spaces are a testament to her skills. The gardens are adorned with vibrant flowers, aromatic herbs, and serene ponds populated by graceful koi fish. Open to the public, they offer respite and wonder to residents and visitors alike.<br><br>Seos proudly upholds the traditions of falconry and archery that have deep roots in the House of Cellesela. The city's skilled archers, feared throughout the empire, showcase their mastery of the bow. Seos' inhabitants share a unique sense of independence, reflecting the free-spirited nature of their governor, Lady Alyna Cerrine. They revel in simple pleasures, including picnics in the gardens, falconry exhibitions, and communal celebrations highlighting the city's agricultural abundance.<br><br>As a vital contributor to the Styx Empire's economy, Seos supplies a surplus of food, wine, and textiles. Its markets brim with fresh produce, locally crafted wines, and finely woven textiles, all of which are eagerly traded with other regions of the empire.<br><br>The legacy of the House of Cellesela lives on in Seos. Creo Ascella, a proud scion of the house, continues to uphold its esteemed traditions. The city also reveres the botanical expertise of Luna Elysia and the artistic contributions of Alyna Cerrine. The House of Cellesela remains a symbol of strength, beauty, and tradition within the Styx Empire.<br>Seos, with its abundant harvests, captivating gardens, and rich cultural heritage, serves as a testament to the prosperity of the Styx Empire and the enduring legacy of the House of Cellesela.]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\cellesela-region\seos.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Cellesela Region/Seos.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Orbis Fortress]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Capital Dominion of Gaius<br>
Orbis Fortress, located within the expansive Tolkhai steppes, serves as a key stronghold and feudal province within the vast dominion of the Styx Empire. As a vassal to the empire, the fortress stands as a crucial administrative center, facilitating the governance and interaction between the ruling powers.<br>Originally a conquered stronghold, Orbis Fortress was transformed into a prominent administrative hub, symbolizing the authority of the Styx Empire within the Tolkhai lands. It serves as the formal seat of the House of Gaius, who govern as feudal lords under the banner of the empire.<br>Despite the traditional nomadic nature of Tolkhai culture, Orbis Fortress stands as a fixed residence, where the House of Gaius holds court and manages the affairs of the feudal province. The fortress serves as a hub for economic activity, trade agreements, and the implementation of imperial policies within the region.<br>Orbis Fortress represents the authority and influence of the Styx Empire over the Tolkhai lands, acting as a strategic bastion to maintain stability and uphold imperial rule. The fortress houses garrisons, administrative offices, and the court of the House of Gaius, ensuring the enforcement of imperial law and the collection of tributes.<br>As a feudal province, Orbis Fortress plays a vital role in the broader governance and power structure of the Styx Empire. It serves as a testament to the enduring strength of the empire and its ability to extend its influence across diverse regions and cultures, forging a united realm under its imperial banner.]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\gaius-region\orbis-fortress.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Gaius Region/Orbis Fortress.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pegasus]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\gaius-region\pegasus.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Gaius Region/Pegasus.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aurora]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Capital Dominion of Rhagaia<br>Nestled within the heart of the Styx Empire lies Aurora, a city that exudes an enchanting aura and serves as the capital of the House of Rhagaia. Renowned for its intellectual prestige and vibrant nocturnal allure, Aurora stands as a testament to the pursuit of knowledge and the celebration of life.<br>At the heart of Aurora, the majestic Grand Library stands as a testament to the city's dedication to wisdom and learning. Sponsored and funded generously by the Rhagaia nobles, it draws scholars and seekers of knowledge from far and wide. Within its hallowed halls reside countless books, manuscripts, and scrolls, their ancient wisdom held in high regard. The library serves as a haven of intellectual exploration, inspiring both residents and visitors to delve into the depths of knowledge.<br>As twilight descends upon Aurora, the city undergoes a captivating transformation. A mesmerizing display of green lights illuminates the streets, casting an ethereal glow reminiscent of flickering fireflies. These enchanting lights guide the way, creating an otherworldly atmosphere that infuses the city with an aura of magic and mystery.<br>The nocturnal residents of Aurora come alive as darkness falls, their vibrant energy infusing the city with a sense of celebration. Bustling markets and lively taverns offer an array of delights, from music and laughter to animated conversations that dance upon the night breeze. The city becomes a stage for enchanting performances, with street artists captivating audiences with their talents and theaters showcasing captivating shows that transport spectators to realms of wonder and imagination.<br>Aurora's architecture echoes its enchanting nature. Elaborate facades adorned with intricate carvings and vibrant colors tell stories of a rich cultural heritage. Narrow cobblestone streets wind through the city, leading explorers to hidden nooks and crannies where secrets and inspiration await.<br>Deeply rooted in Aurora's charm are the Rhagaia nobles, revered for their philosophical nature and pursuit of wisdom. Their wisdom and understanding have earned them respect throughout the empire, as they actively support groundbreaking research and encourage intellectual discourse. The House of Rhagaia stands as a guiding light, inspiring the citizens of Aurora to seek knowledge and embrace a life of intellectual exploration.<br>Aurora, The Enchanted City, casts a spell over all who enter its mystical domain. It beckons with its shimmering green lights, inviting residents and visitors to partake in the vibrant festivities of the night.<br>Caravans often waits outside of city gates where resident still sleeps on day, when night follows the gate are opened and merchants can packed their camp to stay inside.]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\aurora.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Aurora.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coatla]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Current Capital of Malazaer]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\coatla.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Coatla.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Heromur]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>In the realm of the Lynx Kingdom, the capital city of Heromur, known as The Guardian Embrace, stands as a testament to a glorious past overshadowed by the passage of time. The city's defining feature is a towering statue, reminiscent of the legendary Colossus of Rhodes, known as The Guardian Embrace, which stands as a solemn guardian over the city.<br>Approaching Heromur, one can still catch glimpses of its former grandeur, albeit tinged with a sense of fading splendor. The city's architecture carries echoes of its glorious past, with ornate facades and elegant structures that harken back to a time when Heromur was a beacon of opulence and power.<br>While Heromur has not succumbed to total decay, the passage of time has taken its toll. Some buildings bear signs of wear and weathering, their once vibrant colors faded. Cracks and repairs hint at the challenges faced by the city, reminding visitors of the ebb and flow of fortunes over the years. However, amidst this gradual decline, there are pockets of restoration and revitalization, showcasing the city's resilience.<br>The Guardian Embrace, the colossal statue that presides over Heromur, stands as a symbol of the city's enduring spirit. While time may have dulled its luster, the statue's magnificence and imposing presence still inspire a sense of awe and reverence. It serves as a reminder of the city's past glories and the need to protect and cherish its heritage.<br>As one navigates through the city, the streets tell stories of a once-great hub of culture and trade. Though not as bustling as in its heyday, Heromur's markets and bazaars still offer an array of goods, from local crafts to exotic imports. The fragrant aroma of spices and the sound of merchants' calls still fill the air, albeit in a more subdued manner.<br>The city's landmarks, while not as pristine as they once were, still hold a sense of significance. The Royal Palace, though showing signs of age, stands as a testament to the kingdom's history and governance. The Great Library, though slightly diminished, remains a treasure trove of knowledge and a hub for scholars seeking wisdom and enlightenment.<br>Heromur's harbor, once a bustling gateway to distant lands, still maintains a semblance of activity. Ships dock and depart, carrying goods and stories to and from the city. The harbor's energy may not match its former glory, but it retains a vital connection to the world beyond, offering a glimpse into the city's ongoing engagement with the larger realm.<br>While Heromur may not have regained its former status as a great city, it continues to evolve and adapt. New businesses and creative endeavors emerge, breathing life into the streets and injecting fresh energy into the community. The people of Heromur, proud of their heritage, strive to honor their city's past while embracing the challenges of the present.<br>Heromur, The Guardian Embrace, stands as a testament to the cyclical nature of history and the resilience of its inhabitants. It may have lost some of its former glory, but the city's spirit remains steadfast, anchored by the watchful gaze of The Guardian Embrace. Within its streets, visitors can still sense the echoes of a vibrant past and the unwavering determination to carve a new future.]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\heromur.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Heromur.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nepolis]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Current Capital of Sciatic League]]></description><link>places\cities-&amp;-town\nepolis.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Cities &amp; Town/Nepolis.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Azalel]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>places\azalel.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Azalel.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Colonia]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Colonia, the second continent, The lands are ruled by bandits and small warlords, who jockey for control and power in an ongoing struggle for dominance. The Styx Empire, with its armies and resources, has been slowly centralizing its control over Colonia, but the fight for power is far from over. The northern east part of Colonia is home to the great kingdom of Malazaer, now in its exile and remnants of its former glory.]]></description><link>places\colonia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Colonia.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fountain of Youth]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="OldBuilding.jpg" src="lib\media\oldbuilding.jpg"><br>
The story of the Fountain of Youth is intertwined with the history of the Styx Empire.<br>The local natives initially stumbled upon the geyser, which they used for entertainment purposes by inhaling the helium that was released, causing high-pitched squeaks and giggles. Over time, the people began to notice that those who regularly consumed the water from the geyser did not age, maintaining their youth and vitality, while their peers grew old and withered away. This realization fueled a massive demand for the water, as people sought to extend their own lives and enjoy the benefits of immortality.<br>The increased demand for the water from the Fountain of Youth put a strain on the limited resource, causing the efficiency of the geyser to decline. It was at this juncture that the Styx Kings intervened, seeking to regulate consumption and increase efficiency.<br>However, this seemingly perfect solution came with a cost. The water from the Fountain of Youth has a side effect that causes infertility, preventing those who drink from having children. This has led to a decline in the population of the Styx Empire, as the noble families are unable to produce offspring to continue their lineages. Despite this, the desire for eternal youth and vitality among the nobles outweighs the consequences of infertility, and they continue to consume the water from the Fountain.<br>This has resulted in a stark divide between the rulers and the ruled, with the nobles clinging to their power and youth, while the common people face the inevitability of aging and death. The monopoly on the Fountain of Youth has become a symbol of the inequality and injustice within the Styx Empire and has fueled unrest among the vassals.<br>In response to the infertility crisis, the nobles of the Styx Empire have adopted children from among the best and brightest of the vassals, naming them after themselves and numbering them to differentiate between generations. This allows them to continue their household name and maintain the continuity of their lineages, ensuring that their name remains immortal, this system has further entrenched the divide between the nobles and the vassals, as the adopted children are often seen as mere vessels for the continuation of the noble lineages, rather than individuals in their own right. This has resulted in a closed and exclusive society of the nobility, perpetuating their own power and influence for generations to come.]]></description><link>places\fountain-of-youth.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Fountain of Youth.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\oldbuilding.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\oldbuilding.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ashland Region]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>places\the-ashland-region.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/The Ashland Region.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dominar of Empire]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Dominar is the ruler of a Dominion managing the estate of the empire by hereditary]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\dominar-of-empire.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Dominar of Empire.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elite Troops and Mercenary]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Crimson Battalions, Royal Vanguard, Iron Legion]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\elite-troops-and-mercenary.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Elite Troops and Mercenary.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Emperor]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\emperor.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Emperor.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Field Marshal of the King_s Troops]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Field Marshal of the King's Troops&nbsp;is a high-ranking position within the military hierarchy of the Styx Empire. The role is restricted to members of the Trianite Dynasty and is responsible for commanding the Royal Armies in times of conflict. The Field Marshal serves as a rallying point for the armies and is tasked with maintaining the morale and cohesion of the troops.<br>Some of the key duties and responsibilities of the Field Marshal of the King's Troops include:<br>
<br>Commanding the Royal Armies in battle
<br>Maintaining the morale and cohesion of the troops
<br>Acting as a rallying point for the armies
<br>Ensuring the Royal Armies are properly equipped and trained
<br>Collaborating with the High Commander of the Forces to devise and implement military strategies
<br>Advising the ruling monarch on matters related to military and defense
<br>Overseeing the management and administration of the Royal Armies
<br>Only members of the Trianite Dynasty are eligible to hold the position of Field Marshal, making it a coveted and prestigious role within the Styx Empire's military hierarchy.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\field-marshal-of-the-king_s-troops.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Field Marshal of the King_s Troops.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Grand Justiciar]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\grand-justiciar.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Grand Justiciar.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Grand Overseer of Royal Treasure]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Grand Overseer of Royal Treasure&nbsp;is a high-ranking government official in charge of the country's finances and economic policies. This position is responsible for managing the government's revenue and expenses and overseeing the administration of the financial court bureaucracy. The Grand Overseer is tasked with preparing the annual budget and advising the Emperor on financial matters. This position holds a great deal of influence and is considered one of the most important in the government. The Grand Overseer plays a key role in shaping the financial policies of the empire and ensuring that they align with the government's overall strategy and goals.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\grand-overseer-of-royal-treasure.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Grand Overseer of Royal Treasure.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[High Commander of the Forces]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The High Commander of the Forces&nbsp;is a position in the Royal Court responsible for leading and commanding the knight forces in the field. This person is tasked with making strategic and tactical decisions, ensuring that the army is properly equipped and trained, and leading the military in times of war.<br>Responsibilities:<br>
<br>Leading and commanding the knight forces in the field
<br>Making strategic and tactical decisions
<br>Ensuring the readiness of the army
<br>Leading the military in times of war.
]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\high-commander-of-the-forces.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/High Commander of the Forces.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[High Master of Diplomatic Affairs]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>High Master of Diplomatic Affairs&nbsp;is a high-ranking official responsible for managing the Empire's relations with Allies, negotiating treaties and alliances with other nations, and representing the Empire in international forums.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\high-master-of-diplomatic-affairs.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/High Master of Diplomatic Affairs.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keeper of the King_s Purse]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Keeper of the King's Purse - responsible for the safekeeping of the empire's wealth, including gold and precious gems.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\keeper-of-the-king_s-purse.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Keeper of the King_s Purse.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keeper of the Royal Seals]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Keeper of the Royal Seals: Responsible for the safekeeping of the empire official seals and documents.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\keeper-of-the-royal-seals.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Keeper of the Royal Seals.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keeper of the Seals]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\keeper-of-the-seals.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Keeper of the Seals.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Master of Envoys]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Master of Envoys&nbsp;is a crucial member of the Empire's diplomatic corps, responsible for executing foreign policy initiatives and representing the Empire in the field. As an assistant to the High Master of Diplomatic Affairs, the Master of Envoys is responsible for negotiating treaties, maintaining alliances, and bringing news back to the Empire in times of crisis. This position requires a keen understanding of international relations, excellent negotiating skills, and a deep commitment to the goals and interests of the Empire.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\master-of-envoys.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Master of Envoys.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Master of Revenue]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Master of Revenue&nbsp;- responsible for collecting taxes and revenue on behalf of the empire, ensuring that all revenue streams are optimized.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\master-of-revenue.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Master of Revenue.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Master of Royal Funds]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Manages the financial affairs of the imperial court, including paying salaries and expenses.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\master-of-royal-funds.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Master of Royal Funds.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Master of the Mint]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Master of the Mint: Responsible for minting the currency of the empire and ensuring its stability.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\master-of-the-mint.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Master of the Mint.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Royal Auditor]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\royal-auditor.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Royal Auditor.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Royal Justiciar]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Royal Justiciar: The highest judicial officer of the kingdom, responsible for overseeing the administration of justice and interpreting the laws of the kingdom.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\royal-justiciar.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Royal Justiciar.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Support Unit]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>from Servus and managing Sentries/Sentinels and Supply?]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\support-unit.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Support Unit.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Imperial Advisor]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Imperial Advisor&nbsp;is an advisor to the Emperor, providing counsel and guidance on important matters of state. The Imperial Advisor typically holds a high level of influence and is responsible for advising the Emperor on a wide range of policy and governance issues.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\the-imperial-advisor.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/The Imperial Advisor.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Master of War and Military Affairs]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\the-master-of-war-and-military-affairs.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/The Master of War and Military Affairs.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Treasurer_s Aide]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Assists the Grand Overseer of Royal Treasure in managing the finances of the empire and is responsible for tracking treasury.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\treasurer_s-aide.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Treasurer_s Aide.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Warden of the Staple]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Warden of the Staple: In charge of the storage and distribution of important commodities, such as vitales.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\warden-of-the-staple.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Warden of the Staple.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Warlord of the Realm]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Warlord of the Realm&nbsp;is a title used in the Styx Empire to refer to the leader of a vassal army. This individual is responsible for ensuring that their army follows the plans and directives set forth by the High Commander of the Forces. The Warlord is a key figure in maintaining the strength and unity of the empire's military, as well as contributing to the success of military operations.<br>Duties and Responsibilities:<br>
<br>Ensure that their army follows the plans set forth by the High Commander of the Forces
<br>Maintain the strength and unity of the vassal army
<br>Contribute to the success of military operations
<br>Communicate effectively with the High Commander and other military leaders to coordinate efforts and resources.
<br>The Warlord of the Realm plays a crucial role in the Styx Empire's military operations and helps to ensure the success of their armies in the field. As a high-ranking official in the Royal Court, the Warlord is expected to display the highest level of leadership and strategic thinking, and to act in the best interests of the empire and its citizens.]]></description><link>political-realm\court-position\warlord-of-the-realm.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Court Position/Warlord of the Realm.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lynx Kingdom]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Historical names Lineria kingdom before subjugated by Styx]]></description><link>political-realm\lynx-kingdom.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Lynx Kingdom.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Malazaer]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>based on syrian and persian empire]]></description><link>political-realm\malazaer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Malazaer.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Royal Conquest - The Free East]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>is a territorial claim of Styx Empire that are yet to be enforced. many kingdoms, tribes exist in this region.]]></description><link>political-realm\royal-conquest-the-free-east.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Royal Conquest - The Free East.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sciatic League]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="sciatic.jpg" src="lib\media\sciatic.jpg">The Sciatic League&nbsp;is a newly formed alliance of minor Houses located in the secondary northern continent of Colonia. It is known for its massive merchant and armed fleet that dominates the seas, trading in the new resources of the continent recently conquered by the Styx Empire. The league is comprised of several noble houses, including the Noble Fabius Dominic, Noble Sergius Klaus, and Noble Marcuds in the eastern part of the League, and House of Vjokslav in the western part, which holds the capital city of&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Nepolis" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Nepolis" target="_blank">Nepolis</a>.<br>The Sciatic League is renowned for its wealth, which it has acquired through its extensive trading activities. The majority of its nobility come from merchants and artisans, and their culture is based on sea trade, where they mainly deal in exotic products. They are also responsible for producing the most ships for the Styx Empire, with their military forces primarily consisting of a navy. The major exports of the Sciatic League include exotic products and slaves, which is a source of both wealth and controversy.<br>However, the Sciatic League is also known for its piracy issues, which have become a major problem for the League and its merchants. Despite this, the League remains a significant player in the politics and economy of the Styx Empire, and its noble houses continue to wield significant power and influence. With its rich history, culture, and wealth, the Sciatic League is a unique and important part of the Styx Empire.]]></description><link>political-realm\sciatic-league.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Sciatic League.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\sciatic.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\sciatic.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Styx Empire]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Styx Empire&nbsp;is a powerful nation located on the main continent of "Continenta." It was founded by Croton Alycon and has grown over the years to become one of the dominant powers on the continent. The empire is currently ruled by the Trianite Dynasty, with Emperor Ciro Alcyon at its head.<br>The Styx Empire has vassalized the&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Lynx%20Kingdom" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Lynx%20Kingdom" target="_blank">Lynx Kingdom</a>&nbsp;and the&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Sciatic%20League" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Sciatic%20League" target="_blank">Sciatic League</a>, and three nobles manage its territories. This centralization of power has allowed the empire to exert its influence over a vast area, bringing many territories under its control.<br>One of the key strategies used by&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Croton%20Alcyon%20%F0%9F%92%80" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Croton%20Alcyon%20%F0%9F%92%80" target="_blank">Croton Alycon</a>&nbsp;in the early days of the empire was to offer land to anyone who could claim it. This resulted in a massive expansion of Styxian territory, as many people sought to claim land for themselves. Over time, however, the empire centralized its power, either by force, influence, or the sheer goal of defending itself from other powerful landholders.<br>One of the most significant events in the history of the Styx Empire was its conquest of the great&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Malazaer" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Malazaer" target="_blank">kingdom of Malazaer</a>, located on the second continent of "<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Continents" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://continenta.tiddlyhost.com/#Continents" target="_blank">Colonia</a>." The defeat of Malazaer allowed the Styx Empire to gain a foothold on this new continent and establish its dominance over a vast area. Although the former kingdom of Malazaer is now exiled to the northern reaches of Colonia, it remains a shadow of its former glory.<br>Today, the Styx Empire is a symbol of civilization and power on the main continent of Continenta. Its centralization of power and successful expansion into Colonia have secured its place as one of the dominant powers in the world.<br> - Political Hierarchy -]]></description><link>political-realm\styx-empire.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Political Realm/Styx Empire.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Myth of Origin]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Once upon a time, in a old world of Continenta, there existed a legend about five children from different tribes who found themselves intertwined in a hunting expedition. <br>In the heart of the wilderness, these five children embarked on a hunting expedition, unknowingly targeting the same elusive creature. Their desire to possess the animal grew strong, yet none of them were willing to share their ambition. As destiny would have it, their hunt ended in vain. Exhausted, hungry, and disheartened, the children stumbled upon an old man deep within the forest.<br>The old man, sensing their despair, made them an offer: he would provide them with food, but only if they promised to share their experiences of the world with him. Eager to quench their hunger, the children quickly agreed. The old man, satisfied with their promise, led them to a spring where they were rejuvenated by its waters.<br>That very day, as the children emerged from the spring, they found themselves bestowed with extraordinary gifts. Gaius, was gifted a horse. Cellesela, was granted the power of Life, enabling her to breathe life into the dying. Cassio, received a Staff that possessed the ability to transform the land beneath it into pure gold. Rhagaia, acquired the secrets wisdom of people long gone past. Finally, Tyrannia, was given a prophecy.<br>As time went on, None of them aged, They became known as the "Children of Destiny,". They were told to journey to different land of Continenta, where the people still believed in the ancient legends and welcomed the tales of their adventures.<br>Generations passed, and the world evolved, but only people of Tolkhai remained true to their beliefs, never settling in one place. They continued their nomadic lifestyle, forever driven by a thirst for knowledge and a longing to reunite with the old man. And so, the legend lives on, with the hope that one day the promise will return, sharing their extraordinary experiences with the people of Tolkhai, forever bound by an unbreakable bond of exploration and storytelling.]]></description><link>religion\myth-of-origin.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Religion/Myth of Origin.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Song of the Elder Ones]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Religious group that believes in <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Myth of Origin" data-href="Myth of Origin" href="religion\myth-of-origin.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Origin Myth</a> majority comes from the Tolkhai People]]></description><link>religion\song-of-the-elder-ones.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Religion/Song of the Elder Ones.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ori]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Factions/The Ori" data-href="Factions/The Ori" href="factions\the-ori.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Ori</a>]]></description><link>religion\the-ori.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Religion/The Ori.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[- Prologue - World Of Continenta]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
And all youth shall abide<br>
As unforeseen death may die.<br>
Become trivial, such as sleeping,<br>
And become the master of living.<br>
~Tales of Sakkan 6:6
<br> 100 years after the founding king, the Styx Empire rules many nations, but cannot rule itself. The city is always roiled by conflict between the nobility. Power used to be shared, and order maintained by two soldiers, old friends: Croton Alcyon and Julius Cato. Once, Croton was acknowledged by all to be the greater man, but for the last eight years, while Croton has kept the peace in Minerva, Cato has waged a war of conquest in Gaius that has made him ever richer and more popular. The balance of power is shifting, and the nobility have grown fearful. Though of noble blood himself, Cato stands with the common people. A man like that, an aristocrat with soldiers, money, and the love of the people, might make himself the Emperor.<br>But the delicate balance of power in the Styx Empire was not destined to last. A sudden and unexpected threat emerged in the form of the Linerian Army remnant, who sought to reclaim their conquered land.<br>The fragile peace that had held the Styx Empire together for decades shattered like glass when the Linerian Army remnants, long thought to be a spent force, surged forth from the shadows of their conquered lands. Their sudden resurgence caught the empire off guard, and the nobility, so often divided by their petty rivalries, found themselves united by a common enemy. The Linerians fought desperately, their ranks filled with soldiers who had nothing left to lose. As they sought to reclaim their land.<br>But soon the tide of war changes when the battle was followed by an ambush for croton, not a clash of equals but a massacre. The Linerians, though outnumbered, exploited the disarray within the imperial forces. Croton Alcyon, the stalwart defender of Minerva and the man who had once been hailed as the empire's greatest soldier, led his troops into the fray with his characteristic valor. But valor alone could not stem the tide of chaos. Surrounded and overwhelmed, Croton fell, his death as sudden as it was tragic. The man who once been a pillar of stability for the empire was gone, and with him, the last fragile balance of power crumbled.<br>Julius Cato, who had been waging his own war of conquest in Gaius, returned to Minerva upon hearing of Croton's death. The city was in turmoil, the streets filled with cries of the grieving woman and the fearful merchants. Cato, ever the pragmatist, saw an opportunity amidst the chaos. With Croton gone, the nobility were leaderless and desperate. Cato, though he had long positioned himself as a man of the people, knew that the empire needed a strong hand to guide it through the storm. And so, he declared a new edict, one that would reshape the future of the Styx Empire.<br>The edict was as ruthless as it was ingenious. To ensure the continuity of the empire's leadership, Cato decreed that the children of the people of the empire would be taken and raised as heirs to the immortal aristocracy, no matter their background. These children, stripped of their families and their pasts, would be molded into continuation of the empire, their futures bound to its survival. It was a controversial move, one that even sparked outrage among the nobility, but Cato's grip on power was unyielding. The war with the Linerians had left the empire vulnerable, and Cato knew that unity, however forced, was the only path to survival.<br>Among the children taken was Ciro Alcyon, the young son of a humble knight. Though barely more than a boy, Ciro bore the weight of his father's legacy. The boy was a symbol, a living reminder of Croton's sacrifice, and Cato knew that the people would rally behind him. When the war finally ended, with the Linerians driven back and their lands once again under imperial control, Cato made his move. He declared Ciro Alcyon I as the new emperor, a figurehead behind whom the empire could unite.<br>But Ciro's ascension was not without its challenges. The nobility, though cowed by Cato's edict, chafed under the new order. The common people, while they revered Croton's memory, were wary of Cato's growing influence. And Ciro himself, thrust into a role he had never asked for, struggled to find his place in a world shaped by the ambitions of others.<br><br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 1 - Start of the Rift (AI)" data-href="Chapter 1 - Start of the Rift (AI)" href="Chapter 1 - Start of the Rift (AI)" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Continue</a>]]></description><link>remote-blog\publish\story\-prologue-world-of-continenta.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/publish/Story/- Prologue - World Of Continenta.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 13:01:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chapter 1 - Start of the Rift]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br> In solemn hall where councillor represent their house interest. A lady by the name of Azullia Ryea of House Cellesela, the current High Master of Diplomatic Affairs stood, infront of her sit upon the extravagant throne was the emperor himself, The Emperor Ciro Alcyon of the Tyrannite ruling dynasty and surrounding her side is each representative of the other 3 great houses of Styria, this hall is usually calm but recent event revolving around a scandal of a coup by the ruling family itself has set the atmosphere rather tense.
 <br><br>"Your Majesties, esteemed courtiers, I stand before all with matters of great importance, burdened with the scales of a heavy truths that resides within treachery. Potii Taygetta, Together with 3 distinguished nobles of Lynx —Lexius Necca and Semi Lya and the rotten greed Cheh Zardavee have collaborated in secret during the 4th Styx-Lynx War."The courtiers leaned forward, their curiosity piqued by Azullia's words. The air itself seemed to hold its breath, eager to hear the secrets that were about to be revealed."Their alliances have bid linerian along with songs to weaken our independence. his action have left our empire with tremendous price of political and costly economic reparations."The courtiers exchanged glances, procedded by the once silence room to disapproving noises, A hushed silence descended upon the court, the weight of Azullia's words hangs in the air.Oh, how our fate has intertwined in their destinies, Together, they conspired in deceit, encouraging Lynx's audacious bid to take back our independence, seeking to free themselves from the embrace of Styx's powerful influence. Alas, their actions have cast a lingering shadow of burden upon our noble empire, forcing us to endure the weighty reparations that still haunt our coffers."Whispers of disbelief rippled through the court as the gravity of the situation settled upon them. All eyes turned to Potii Taygetta, Potii Taygetta stood there, seemingly composed, yet his eyes flickered with a hint of unease. He understood the gravity of the situation, knowing that Azullia's silver-tongued rhetoric had placed him at the center of a narrative he might struggle to escape.Taygetta's eyes met those of Ciro Alycon, a signal mix of remorse and plea evident within them."Your Majesty, I stand before you with a heavy heart and a burdened conscience. I assure you, the accusations laid upon me are not as they seem. There are complexities at play, intricacies of loyalty and unforeseen alliances that I must shed light upon."Ciro Alycon's face displayed a myriad of emotions—doubt, concern, and maybe a glimmer of hope."You ask for understanding, even as the evidence against you mounts. My heart is torn, for I cannot easily cast aside the bond we share. However, the accusations brought forth demand resolution, and the unity of our empire must take precedence."The court murmured with dissent, Zeurgeud, the known richest noble of the empire, voicing his discontent and demanding swift judgment.Zeurgeud: "Your Majesty, we cannot afford to stall. The betrayal is clear, and the empire's dignity must be restored."Julius Cato, the trusted commander of the empire, stepped forward with a measured tone."Respected Monarch, I understand Zeurgeud's concerns, but we must tread cautiously. Potii Taygetta's position as 'The Ori' and the intricacies of his role in the Imperial Cult religion warrant a thorough investigation. Rushing to judgment may lead the <a data-href="The Common Onwixe (unwise)" href="creature\the-common-onwixe-(unwise).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Common Onwixe (unwise)</a> towards doubting your reigns.""I hear your concerns, Zeurgeud, and I value your counsel, Julius Cato. Yet, we cannot ignore the complexities of this situation. I request Lawbringer and hold a private audience with Noble Taygetta to hear his side formally. Only then can we make an informed decision."The court erupted into a mix of reactions, with most expressing dissatisfaction and others acknowledging Ciro Alycon's words. |"This matter requires careful deliberation, Let it be known that this court shall be paused temporarily.The court will then reconvene once we have gathered all relevant information. Noble Taygetta, I implore you to present any evidence or explanations that may sway my judgment. Until then, no judgement will pass."Ciro Alycon, burdened by conflicting emotions, watched as the court dispersed, the voices of nobles echoing through the grand chamber. The fate of Potii Taygetta, his cousin and a figure both revered and feared, now hung in the balance. He knows of his treacherous act and knew of his ambitious power hungry nature, yet, he wont be able to render judgement without bias, mainly not of its political consequences but rather his familial relationship with Taygetta, he won't able to imagine sons of Minerca would be held responsible for treachery and hanged in public like a commonner.<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 2 - The Cellesella (AI)" data-href="Chapter 2 - The Cellesella (AI)" href="remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-2-the-cellesella-(ai).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow"><span class="iconize-icon-in-link" title="🤖" aria-label="🤖" data-icon="🤖" aria-hidden="true" style="transform: translateY(0px);"></span>Continue To Chapter II</a>🤖]]></description><link>remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-1-start-of-the-rift.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/publish/Story/Chapter 1 - Start of the Rift.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 14:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chapter 2 - The Cellesella]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>A few months before the court meeting, in the opulent chambers of Hyperia, the capital city of <a data-href="House Cellesela" href="House Cellesela" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">House Cellesela</a>, a chilling conversation unfolded between Ascella, a young nobleman unaccustomed to the intricacies of politics, and Octavia Vulp, Creo Ascella oldest sister and the mind of House Cellesela. The room was adorned with exquisite tapestries, vibrant hues reflecting the mosaic glass of its windows.<br>Octavia's gaze fell upon Ascella, her voice with icy authority spoke. "Creo, it is time for you to embark on a journey to Minerva, the heart of The Empire. House Cellesela would requires your presence there."<br>Ascella, his voice barely above a whisper, shuffled uneasily in his stance. His young heart and lack of political experience left him conflicted, but he dared not defy his sister's command. "Octavia, I-I am honored by your trust in me. B-But Minerva... unlike the warmth and simplicity of our home in Hyperia. I fear I am ill-prepared for-."<br>Octavia's lips curved into a chilling smile, her voice gentle yet resolute. "Dear Creo, I understand. Minerva can be a treacherous place, but it is precisely because of your purity of heart and untainted perspective that you are needed there. Your innocence will be your greatest strength, I will need you there."<br>Ascella lowered his gaze, his voice with uncertainty. "But Octavia, what if I fail? What if I am swallowed whole? I fear I may not possess the astuteness and wit as yours."<br>Octavia's eyes gleamed. "Creo, my dear brother, survival in Minerva requires more than just cunning and ruthlessness, Do not doubt yourself. You may lack experience, but trust me, I shall be watching closely."<br>Ascella looked up, meeting Octavia's gaze with a mix of uncertainty and resignation. "I-I may have no choice, Octavia, I will go to Minerva."<br>Octavia's face softened, a proud smile gracing her lips. "That is the spirit, Ascella.&nbsp;Your presence will bring a breath of fresh air to the court, a glimmer of hope amidst the darkness. Remember, you possess a rare gift—a pure and innocent heart that cannot be tarnished by corrupted power. Embrace this gift, and let it guide your actions in the days to come."<br>As the morning sun cast a golden glow over Hyperia, Creo Ascella prepared for his departure to the treacherous world of Minerva. His heart weighed heavy with uncertainty, yet a spark of determination flickered within him. The courtyard of the Cellesela Palace buzzed with activity, servants scurrying around to gather his belongings and prepare the litter that would carry him to his destination.<br>Creo stood at the threshold, donning a tailored cloak that bore the emblem of House Cellesela. Octavia, adorned in her regal attire, emerged from the shadows, her demeanor cool and calculated. Her gaze met Creo's, a mix of expectation and calculated concern.<br>Remember, Creo," Octavia spoke softly, "you carry the weight of our house upon your shoulders. Minerva is a viper's nest, with cunning courtiers and power-hungry aristocrats. Do not falter, for the fate of House Cellesela rests in your hands."<br>Creo nodded, his voice soft as he replied, "I understand. I will do my best to uphold house honour."<br>With those last words, Creo climbed into the luxurious carriage, his heart pounds with anxiety. The silk curtains were drawn closed, enveloping him in a dimly-lit cocoon of solitude as the wheels began to turn and set towards the capital city.<br>Creo journey was arduous, with the carriage swaying along winding roads. Creo caught glimpses of the changing landscapes from small openings in the curtains, as idyllic views of Hyperia transitioned into bustling towns and finally the grandeur of the imperial capital.<br>As the carriage came to a halt, Creo's heart skipped a beat. he take a step outside of the curtain and saw he at the city gates, The imposing figure of a guard approached, clad in heavy armor decorated with the emblem of the empire. The guard about to investigate the caravan and its occupants before a realization dawned upon him.<br>"Creo Ascella, of House Cellesela, correct?" the guard inquired, his tone respectful yet firm.<br>Creo nodded, his voice barely a whisper. "Yes"<br>A small smile tugged at the corner of the guard's lips. "Welcome to Minerva, young noble. I have been informed of your arrival. Please allow me to guide you to your final destination, the Emperor Palace."<br>Followed by relief, Creo carriage followed the guard as they made their way through the bustling streets of Minerva. The city's sights and sounds overwhelmed him, the distant sounds of the bustling market start to reached his ears. The lively exchanges between merchants and customers but he soon found solace in the guard's presence.<br>As the carriage came to a halt near the palace gardens, Creo stepped out and marveled at the serene beauty that surrounded him. Blooming markets painted the landscape in vibrant colors, the sweet fragrance of exotic perfume filling the air. It was a stark contrast to the bustling city he had left behind.<br>Emperor Ciro Alycon, known for his love of nature, awaited Creo in the midst of the lush garden. His warm smile welcomed the young noble, making him feel instantly at ease. The emperor's eyes sparkled with a kindness that Creo had not expected from a ruler of such stature.<br>"Creo Ascella, scion of House Cellesela, I bid you welcome," Emperor Ciro Alycon greeted, his voice gentle yet filled with a jovial undertone. He chuckled softly and gestured towards the surrounding flowers. "Aren't these gardens a sight to behold? Nature has its own way of brightening our spirits."<br>Creo bowed respectfully. "Your Majesty, I am honored by your gracious welcome. indeed i am in awe on what the palace have."<br>Emperor Ciro Alycon let out a hearty laugh, his voice carrying through the garden. "Ah, I'm glad you appreciate it, young Creo! Sometimes amidst all the turbulent politics and its responsibilities, we need a little dose of nature to remind us of the simple joys in life."<br>Emperor Ciro Alycon placed a hand on Creo's shoulder, his touch warm and friendly. "My young kind, born being chosen might not be an easy one, but I believe in you. You have the determination to bring about change."<br>Creo's face flushed with a mix of excitement and nervousness. The emperor's encouragement put him at ease, allowing his thoughts to surface. "Your Majesty, I am happy for your faith in me. I will try my best to honor my family and contribute to the betterment of the empire."<br>The emperor chuckled again at Creo naivity and laughed. "That's the spirit, Creo! your contribution would be needed by the Empire, now go play with your age, this formality talk would bore even an adult."<br>Creo couldn't help but smile in response to the emperor's jovial response. The journey ahead might be challenging, but with the emperor's guidance and support, Creo was ready to face it with confidence.<br>As the emperor and Creo walked through the flourishing garden, their conversation flowed effortlessly, punctuated by occasional bursts of laughter. Creo found himself sharing anecdotes from his hometown, and the emperor reciprocated with tales of his own adventures.<br>In the midst of their camaraderie, Emperor Ciro Alycon stopped near a blooming magnolia tree and turned to Creo with a mischievous glint in his eyes. "Creo, my young friend, I have a gift for you," he announced, his voice filled with warmth and anticipation.<br><img alt="1675935020913.jpg" src="lib\media\1675935020913.jpg"><br>
From behind the tree, a young woman emerged, her eyes sparkling with curiosity. She was introduced as Elara, a spirited and humble soul who had a deep connection to the empire's people. Ascella's heart skipped a beat as he caught sight of her, captivated by her genuine charm and the aura of mystery that surrounded her.<br>"Elara shall be your companion on this journey, Creo," the emperor declared, his voice filled with fatherly affection. "Her humble wisdom and compassionate nature will be a valuable asset as you navigate the intricacies of the capital and broaden your horizons."<br>A surprise revealed across Creo's face, his cheeks reddened. He bowed respectfully to Elara, expressing his appreciation for her presence. The young woman smiled warmly, her attire simple yet elegant, reflecting her down-to-earth nature.<br>While they continued their walk, Ciro Alycon, the emperor, took Creo to a quiet courtyard, which was decorated with blooming jasmine vines. There was Alcyon II, the young prince who would one day ascend to the emperor throne. The prince shows enthusiasm, eager to meet new boy his age, as he was rarely meet his equals.<br>"Creo, allow me to introduce you to Alcyon II, my esteemed successor," the emperor announced, pride evident in his voice. "He possesses a keen intellect and a deep sense of duty. You will find him to be a great friend and partner while you get accustomed to the court life."<br>Creo showed his respect to the young prince, Alcyon II greeted him with genuine warmth, extending a hand in friendship. It was then and there where Creo comprehended he was a part of a world far bigger than he expected to be.<br>The Emperor Ciro Alycon watched as the three individuals stood together, as laughter filled the garden as they started to play away.<br>The sun setting over the day, a warm glow upon the palace gardens, In this moment, surrounded by meticulous frame of nature and the companionship of new friends, Creo felt an overwhelming sense of gratitude. The path ahead was no longer one he had to tread alone, for he had the support and guidance of Emperor Ciro Alycon, Elara, and the future emperor, Alcyon II.<br>During an elegant ball held in the grand palace room, Elara and Creo find themselves overwhelmed by the enchanting atmosphere. As the room fills with slow romantic melody, Elara's eyes sparkle with a mischievous glint. Without hesitation, she reaches out, gently taking Creo's hand in hers and pulling him towards the dance floor.<br>Creo's heart races as Elara guides him effortlessly through the steps of the dance. They move in harmony, their bodies sway to the rhythm of the music. And as they twirl gracefully, Creo's eyes never leave Elara's, his admiration of her growing with each step, their hearts beating in tandem.<br>Amidst the flickering glow of candlelight, Elara's curiosity gets the better of her. With a smile on her lips, she leans in closer and whispers, "Creo, where did you learn to dance so beautifully?"<br>A tender smile graces Creo's face as he replies, "With my sister. We would twirl and spin around our home, laughing and enjoying each other's company,"<br>In that shared revelation, Elara's eyes soften, The dance becomes more than just a series of steps—it becomes a celebration of the blossoming connection between their hearts.<br>As the music reaches its crescendo, they hold each other closer, their bodies pressed together, and for a brief moment, Time seems to stand still as they share a final, breathless gaze. In that lingering moment, the unspoken promises of their dance hang in the air, leaving them both yearning for more.<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 3 - The Cost of Immortality" data-href="Chapter 3 - The Cost of Immortality" href="remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-3-the-cost-of-immortality.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Next Chapter</a>]]></description><link>remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-2-the-cellesella.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/publish/Story/Chapter 2 - The Cellesella.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 03:05:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\1675935020913.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\1675935020913.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chapter 2 - The Cellesella (AI)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>A few months before the court meeting, in the opulent chambers of Hyperia, the capital city of House Cellesela, a chilling conversation unfolded between Ascella, a young nobleman unaccustomed to the intricacies of politics, and Octavia Vulp, Creo Ascella oldest sister and a shrewd political strategist. The room was adorned with exquisite tapestries, their vibrant hues reflecting the calculated nature of the decisions being made.<br>Octavia's piercing gaze fell upon Ascella, her voice dripping with icy authority. "Creo, it is time for you to embark on a journey to Minerva, the heart of political power in the Styx Empire. House Cellesela requires your presence there to strengthen our influence and shape our future."<br>Ascella, his voice barely above a whisper, shuffled uneasily in his stance. His young heart and lack of political experience left him conflicted, but he dared not defy his sister's command. "O-Octavia, I-I am honored by your trust in me. B-But Minerva... it is a world so unlike the warmth and simplicity of our home in Hyperia. I fear I am ill-prepared for the intrigues and complexities that await me there."<br>Octavia's lips curved into a chilling smile, her voice gentle yet resolute. "Dear Creo, I comprehend your apprehension. Minerva can be a treacherous place, but it is precisely because of your purity of heart and untainted perspective that you are needed there. Your innocence will be your greatest strength, as it will offer a fresh and genuine perspective amidst the cunning and deceit of the court."<br>Ascella lowered his gaze, his voice tinged with uncertainty. "But Octavia, what if I falter? What if I am swallowed whole by the web of lies and power struggles? I fear I may not possess the astuteness and wit required to navigate those dangerous waters."<br>Octavia's eyes gleamed with a mixture of amusement and disdain. "Ascella, my dear brother, survival in Minerva requires more than just cunning and ruthlessness. It requires the ability to wear a mask of charm and deceit, Do not doubt yourself. You may lack experience, but trust me, I shall be watching closely, guiding your every move."<br>Ascella looked up, meeting Octavia's cold gaze with a mixture of uncertainty and resignation. "I-I have no choice but to obey your command, Octavia. Though I am hesitant and filled with doubts, I will venture into the treacherous world of Minerva, armed with the knowledge that my every action will be orchestrated by your hand."<br>Octavia's face softened, a proud smile gracing her lips. "That is the spirit, Ascella.&nbsp;Your presence will bring a breath of fresh air to the court, a glimmer of hope amidst the darkness. Remember, you possess a rare gift—a pure and innocent heart that cannot be tarnished by the machinations of power. Embrace this gift, and let it guide your actions in the days to come."<br>As the morning sun cast a golden glow over Hyperia, Creo Ascella prepared for his departure to the treacherous world of Minerva. His heart weighed heavy with uncertainty, yet a spark of determination flickered within him. The courtyard of the Cellesela Palace buzzed with activity, servants scurrying around to gather his belongings and prepare the litter that would carry him to his destination.<br>Creo stood at the threshold, donning a tailored cloak that bore the emblem of House Cellesela. Octavia, adorned in her regal attire, emerged from the shadows, her demeanor cool and calculated. Her gaze met Creo's, a mix of expectation and calculated concern.<br>Remember, Creo," Octavia spoke softly, "you carry the weight of our house upon your shoulders. Minerva is a viper's nest, teeming with cunning courtiers and power-hungry aristocrats. Do not falter, for the fate of House Cellesela rests in your hands."<br>Creo nodded, his voice soft as he replied, "I understand, Octavia. I will do my best to navigate the treacherous waters of Minerva and uphold the honor of our house."<br>With those words, Creo climbed into the luxurious litter, his heart pounding with a mix of anticipation and anxiety. The silk curtains were drawn closed, enveloping him in a cocoon of solitude as the litterbearers lifted the contraption and set off towards the capital city.<br>The journey to Minerva was arduous, with the litter swaying along winding roads. Creo caught glimpses of the changing landscapes from small openings in the curtains, as idyllic views of Hyperia transitioned into bustling towns and finally the grandeur of the imperial capital.<br>As the litter came to a halt at the city gates, Creo's heart skipped a beat. The imposing figure of a guard approached, clad in armor adorned with the emblem of the empire. The guard scrutinized the caravan and its occupants before a realization dawned upon him.<br>"Creo Ascella, of House Cellesela, correct?" the guard inquired, his tone respectful yet firm.<br>Creo nodded, his voice barely a whisper. "Yes, that is correct."<br>A small smile tugged at the corner of the guard's lips. "Welcome to Minerva, young noble. I have been informed of your arrival. Please allow me to guide you to your final destination, the Palace."<br>With a sense of relief, Creo followed the guard as they made their way through the bustling streets of Minerva. The city's sights and sounds overwhelmed him, the distant sounds of the bustling market reached his ears. The lively exchanges between merchants and customers echoed through the air but he found solace in the guard's presence.<br>As the litter came to a halt near the palace gardens, Creo stepped out and marveled at the serene beauty that surrounded him. Blooming flowers painted the landscape in vibrant colors, their sweet fragrance filling the air. It was a stark contrast to the bustling city he had left behind.<br>Emperor Ciro Alycon, known for his love of nature, awaited Creo in the midst of the lush garden. His warm smile welcomed the young noble, making him feel instantly at ease. The emperor's eyes sparkled with a kindness that Creo had not expected from a ruler of such stature.<br>"Creo Ascella, scion of House Cellesela, I bid you welcome," Emperor Ciro Alycon greeted, his voice gentle yet filled with a jovial undertone. He chuckled softly and gestured towards the surrounding flowers. "Aren't these gardens a sight to behold? Nature has its own way of brightening our spirits."<br>Creo bowed respectfully. "Your Majesty, I am honored by your gracious welcome. Indeed, these gardens are a testament to the beauty and tranquility that the empire encompasses."<br>Emperor Ciro Alycon let out a hearty laugh, his voice carrying through the garden. "Ah, I'm glad you appreciate it, young Creo! Sometimes amidst all the politics and responsibilities, we need a little dose of nature's wonders to remind us of the simple joys in life."<br>Emperor Ciro Alycon placed a hand on Creo's shoulder, his touch warm and friendly. "My young friend, the path you've chosen isn't an easy one, but I believe in you. You have the heart of a dreamer and the determination to bring about positive change."<br>Creo's face flushed with a mix of excitement and nervousness. The emperor's jovial and encouraging demeanor put him at ease, allowing his true thoughts to surface. "Your Majesty, I am grateful for your faith in me. I will do my best to honor my family and contribute to the betterment of the empire."<br>Emperor Ciro Alycon chuckled again, his laughter contagious. "That's the spirit, Creo! Life is indeed a grand adventure, filled with both triumphs and tribulations. It is through our missteps and challenges that we discover our true strength and grow wiser."<br>Creo couldn't help but smile in response to the emperor's infectious laughter and uplifting words. The journey ahead might be challenging, but with the emperor's guidance and support, Creo was ready to face it with renewed confidence.<br>As the emperor and Creo walked through the flourishing garden, their conversation flowed effortlessly, punctuated by occasional bursts of laughter. Creo found himself sharing anecdotes from his hometown, and the emperor reciprocated with tales of his own adventures.<br>In the midst of their camaraderie, Emperor Ciro Alycon stopped near a blooming magnolia tree and turned to Creo with a mischievous glint in his eyes. "Creo, my young friend, I have a gift for you," he announced, his voice filled with warmth and anticipation.<br><img alt="1675935020913.jpg" src="lib\media\1675935020913.jpg"><br>
From behind the tree, a young woman emerged, her eyes sparkling with curiosity. She was introduced as Elara, a spirited and humble soul who had a deep connection to the empire's people. Ascella's heart skipped a beat as he caught sight of her, captivated by her genuine charm and the aura of mystery that surrounded her.<br>"Elara shall be your companion on this journey, Creo," the emperor declared, his voice filled with fatherly affection. "Her humble wisdom and compassionate nature will be a valuable asset as you navigate the intricacies of the capital and broaden your horizons."<br>Creo's cheeks flushed with a mix of surprise and gratitude. He bowed respectfully to Elara, expressing his appreciation for her presence. The young woman smiled warmly, her attire simple yet elegant, reflecting her down-to-earth nature.<br>As they continued their leisurely stroll, Emperor Ciro Alycon guided Creo towards a tranquil courtyard adorned with blooming jasmine vines. Waiting there was Alcyon II, the young prince who would one day ascend to the throne. The prince exuded an air of youthful enthusiasm, eager to learn and make his mark on the empire.<br>"Creo, allow me to introduce you to Alcyon II, my esteemed successor," the emperor announced, pride evident in his voice. "He possesses a keen intellect and a deep sense of duty. You will find in him a valuable ally and friend as you navigate the intricacies of court life."<br>Creo offered a respectful bow to the young prince, his gaze filled with admiration. Alcyon II greeted him with genuine warmth, extending a hand in friendship. It was in that moment that Creo realized he had entered a world far grander than he had ever imagined—a world of mentors, companions, and the potential for lifelong friendships.<br>Emperor Ciro Alycon watched with a twinkle in his eye as the three individuals stood together, united by the bonds of shared aspirations and the promise of a brighter future. Laughter filled the garden, interwoven with their conversations, painting a tapestry of hope and possibility.<br>With the sun gently setting in the horizon, casting a warm glow upon the palace gardens, Creo felt an overwhelming sense of gratitude. In this enchanting moment, surrounded by the beauty of nature and the companionship of newfound friends, he knew that his journey had taken a profound turn. The path ahead was no longer one he had to tread alone, for he had the support and guidance of Emperor Ciro Alycon, the humble and enigmatic Elara, and the future ruler, Alcyon II.<br>During an elegant ball held in the grand ballroom, Elara and Creo find themselves captivated by the enchanting atmosphere. As the room fills with the sound of a slow, romantic melody, Elara's eyes sparkle with a mischievous glint. Without hesitation, she reaches out, gently taking Creo's hand in hers and pulling him towards the dance floor.<br>Creo's heart races as Elara guides him effortlessly through the steps of the dance. They move in perfect harmony, their bodies swaying to the rhythm of the music. As they twirl gracefully, Creo's eyes never leave Elara's, his admiration for her growing with each step, their hearts beating in tandem.<br>Amidst the flickering glow of candlelight, Elara's curiosity gets the better of her. With a smile on her lips, she leans in closer and whispers, "Creo, where did you learn to dance so beautifully?"<br>A tender smile graces Creo's face as he replies, "With my sister. We would twirl and spin around our home, laughing and enjoying each other's company,"<br>In that shared revelation, Elara's eyes soften, The dance becomes more than just a series of steps—it becomes a celebration of their shared experiences and the blossoming connection between their hearts.<br>As the music reaches its crescendo, they hold each other closer, their bodies pressed together, and for a fleeting moment, Time seems to stand still as they share a final, breathless gaze. In that lingering moment, the unspoken promises of their dance hang in the air, leaving them both yearning for more.<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 3 - The Cost of Immortality" data-href="Chapter 3 - The Cost of Immortality" href="remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-3-the-cost-of-immortality.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Next Chapter</a>]]></description><link>remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-2-the-cellesella-(ai).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/publish/Story/Chapter 2 - The Cellesella (AI).md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 13:08:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\1675935020913.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\1675935020913.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chapter 3 - The Cost of Immortality]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>In a realm where shadows whispered secrets and the winds carried tales of forgotten lands, the lost knight, Wensbane, found solace in the dimly lit tavern. Glass after glass of ale, he consumed, seeking respite from the weight of his sorrow. A question escaped his lips, a plea for understanding, but the people around him brushed it off with jests and laughter. They could not comprehend the depths of his despair.<br>Amidst the raucous merriment, the barkeeper, a weathered soul who had witnessed countless stories unfold, interjected with a solemn tone. "He's a father of the immortal," he murmured, his voice carrying the weight of untold sorrows.<br>A stranger, drawn by the intrigue, inquired about the noble house that had taken Wensbane son. The barkeeper, with a flicker of sadness in his eyes, revealed, "The king. It is the king who sought his presence."<br>The stranger, contemplative, mused aloud, recognizing the anguish that lay beneath the surface. "To sacrifice a son for the realm one serves... It must be a heavy burden. But why is he here in <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Mineralia Magna" data-href="Mineralia Magna" href="places\cities-&amp;-town\cassio-region\mineralia-magna.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magna</a>?"<br>The barkeeper, his voice laced with a tinge of knowing, replied, "He seeks distance from Continenta, from the very heart of the Empire Capital. For guilt, my friend, has a way of consuming even the bravest souls. It claws at him relentlessly."<br>Caught in the swirl of emotions, the lost knight, his identity concealed by shadows, could not help but interject into the conversation. "One must forget who they are," he murmured pensively, his words veiled in a haunting wisdom.<br>"The Cost of Immortality," he continued, his voice carrying the weight of countless unspoken truths. The silence that followed was heavy with unspoken empathy.<br>"I am <a data-href="Balleon Wensbane" href="character\balleon-wensbane.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Balleon Wensbane</a>," he finally revealed, his voice laced with a mixture of pain and determination. "My son is <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Ciro Alcyon II" data-href="Ciro Alcyon II" href="character\house-of-tyrannite\ciro-alcyon-ii.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Nabeon Wensbane</a>, at least that's the name before they took him."<br>Now they called him <a data-href="Ciro Alcyon II" href="character\house-of-tyrannite\ciro-alcyon-ii.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ciro Alcyon II</a> how did it happen? my loyalty to the emperor was unquestionable. <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Factions/The Ori" data-href="Factions/The Ori" href="factions\the-ori.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Father</a> gifted my son to be part of the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Styx Empire" data-href="Styx Empire" href="political-realm\styx-empire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Heaven</a> serving the empire as its ruler for eternity while he must forget that I was his father and as I aswell to remember him as my son.<br>I was a fool, to give away my only memory of her, while others struggled to give away theirs. but none of it matter; the heaven takes what it wants. and <a data-href="The Mothers" href="factions\the-mothers.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Mothers</a> take theirs.<br>Wensbane hears of all of Mercenary armies marching from Colonia to Continenta, to march against the Ruling Dynasty, soon the streets were filled with prices of every heads of Loyalist who still loyal to Tyrannite, hurried he tried to goes to Capital to saves his son, he gathers comrades of people who are loyal but the gathering is assaulted by Cassio own forces, now hes locked in prison for month until the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Massacre of Tyrannt" data-href="Massacre of Tyrannt" href="massacre-of-tyrannt.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">events</a> happened.<br>Wensbane's heart sank as he heard rumors of the Mercenary armies marching from Colonia to Continenta, their intent to overthrow the Ruling Dynasty. The streets buzzed with fear as such act never happened in their life and grandfather life. The loyalty of the remaining Loyalists who still stood with Tyrannite was being tested, with bounties placed on their heads.<br>Driven by a desperate need to save his son, Wensbane hurriedly made his way to sought out comrades, fellow loyal souls who believed in the Empire and were willing to fight for Honor. Together, they formed a clandestine gathering, united in their determination to protect the Empire while Nabeon still there.<br>But their gathering were assaulted by the very own heaven. Cassio's own forces launched a brutal assault on their gathering. Wensbane fought valiantly, his sword clashing against his enemies, but outnumbered and overwhelmed, he was captured and thrown into a grim cell.<br>Days turned into weeks, and weeks into months, as Wensbane languished in the confines of his prison. The weight of his guilt and the ache of separation from his son gnawed at his soul. Yet, a flicker of hope remained, fueling his determination to defy the chains that held him captive.<br>Little did Wensbane know that the events that would shape his destiny were already set in motion. The wheels of fate were turning, and as he languished in darkness, a wave of changes was brewing on the horizon. The hour of reckoning approached, promising both redemption and new challenges.<br>In the depths of his prison, Wensbane clung to the memory of his son, Nabeon, and the love that bound them. With every passing day, his resolve grew stronger, ready to face the trials ahead and reclaim what was rightfully his.<br>Ciro Alcyon meet a soothsayer telling them the king soon will get his neck bit by a snake.<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 4 - Wave of Changes" data-href="Chapter 4 - Wave of Changes" href="remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-4-wave-of-changes.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Next Chapter</a>]]></description><link>remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-3-the-cost-of-immortality.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/publish/Story/Chapter 3 - The Cost of Immortality.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 14:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chapter 4 - Wave of Changes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Months follow, an entire continent is mobillized towards war. Disgruntled Noble from Cassio and Cellesela, leaded by Rhagaian banner attempt coup against Tyrannite <br>
Azullia Ryea: (clenching her fists) Our cause is just, for we seek to restore honor to our land. We shall bring retribution upon those who have dared to betray us. With my guidance and the aid of other noble houses, we shall strike at the heart of the Tyrannite's power.
<br>Who cames to our call?<br>
Rhagaian Messanger: all but Gaius, your majesty<br>Azullia: the old cato..., the fool..<br>
Martius Umbra: i have prepared for this moment, Sis<br>
the Guild have prepared new Siege Devices to punish the Gaius Main Army
<br>
Azullia: The preparation need to be soon their armies are three times larger than all house combined ,luckly Cassio deep pocket able to reach mercenary from Colonia
<br>the noble conspirators turned to the realm of mercenaries, where swords and loyalty were readily available for the right price. Private armies were moving from Colonia to Continenta, their ranks swelling with mercenaries seeking their own moment of glory and power. The tension mounted, a tempest of unrest brewing beneath the surface.<br>Within the Palace of House Cellesela, All the Lady gathered to discuss the pressing matter at hand.<br>
Lady Luna Elysia: (calmly) Before we rush into war, have we exhausted all diplomatic routes? Perhaps we can negotiate with the Tyrannite or seek alliances with other noble houses who share our grievances.
<br>
Octavia Vulp: (leaning forward, a touch of impatience in her voice) Luna, Cassio and Rhagaian already ammassing armies for war, they didnt want peaceful resolution anymore they want to overthrow Tyrannite rule.
<br>
Alynna Cerrine: what would happen to our brother? hes currently stuck in Minerva while the entire continent want to swallow minerva whole.
<br>
Octavia Vulp: our brother held down by Tyrannite, they asked for us to back down in the upcoming war, however if we didnt join this war then our brother fate are decided by Cassio and Rhagaia which are no better.
<br>
Luna Elysia: oh have mercy Goddess Minerva, poor Creo.
<br>In Minerva Court<br>
Julius Cato: Samulus i need you to gather all the armies to pretect the capital, i will gather our forces to stop Rhagaian armies to pass
<br>
Samulus: Yes, Great Father
<br>Soon Rhagaian and Gaius Army met in Land of the Tolkhai, Flat grassland as far as eye can see.<br>Azullia Ryea armies are 4500 men while Gaius have higher numerical advantage at 7000<br>
with their horses<br>The Rhagaian soon discuss their plan on war tent.<br>
Azullia Ryea: Our Scout counted 7000 more or less are blocking our way to Minerva, i have no doubt that gathering nomadic tribes is more easier than gathering man from a city.
<br>on the other side of the battle are Gaius Army leaded by Julius Cato, an experienced commander and part of the Empire Court<br>The Next day both armies stand side by side in open plains, Rhagaian start their first move by bringing a 100&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="app://obsidian.md/Turtle%20Battlewagon" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="\Turtle Battlewagon" target="_blank">Turtle Battlewagon</a>, an impenetrable moving fortress filled with 8 mounted crossbowmen each and a ballista followed by Spearman marching behind<br>Gaius soon followed with their cavalry of 2000 Man, soon arrows shot by each other side. at first Gaius Cavalry taking the lead until the rhagaian forces showed their Card, Sound of Eagle disturb the battlefield, horse panicked and ignored their Master, rode faster like they seen the death himself, the sound come from none other than from the Bolt of Ballista in <a data-href="Turtle Battlewagon" href="turtle-battlewagon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Turtle Battlewagon</a> metallic arrowhead amplified the sounds that are usually made of horse great predator, <a data-href="The Horned Sea Eagle" href="creature\the-horned-sea-eagle.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Horned Sea Eagle</a>.<br>fallen from their horses, the Cavalry meet their demise pointed by the Crossbowmen, piercing their armor straight to it flesh.<br>the first battle is won by Rhagaian <br>second battle follows the next week<br>Seeing what happen, Julius Cato order the cavalry army to move to a bog region  and as usual <a data-href="Turtle Battlewagon" href="turtle-battlewagon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Turtle Battlewagon</a> followed<br>
them with Spearmen<br>
Julius ordered them to dismount their horses <br>Rhagaian Armies soon seen an opportunity to encircle Gaius Army in Shallow Water.<br>
Azzulia Ryea: Blow the Horn, bring Cato to me.
<br>The sounds of War Horn swept across the battlefield, Rhagaian main armies now joined the battle, However after most of their armies followed.<br>
Julius Cato: Men!, GET BACK TO YOUR HORSES!
<br>The cavalry mount and retreat back while flaming arrow flew over them and fireball rolling from the sides setting the tallgrass on fire<br>
Cooking the person inside the <a data-href="Turtle Battlewagon" href="turtle-battlewagon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Turtle Battlewagon</a>.<br>Realizing they were now trapped the Rhagaian armies broke apart and are defeated and the rest march back.<br>The Battle are won by The Empire.<br>Ensues leading to a massacre of ... when army loyal to the emperor are overwhelmed 10:1 unable to amass support faster than Private Armies<br>The noble killed successor of Tyrannite, making the death of First Immortal, Rest of Tyrannite Dynasty member moved to Colonia for their own safety<br>Ascella sadded by death of his only friend <a data-href="Ciro Alcyon II" href="character\house-of-tyrannite\ciro-alcyon-ii.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ciro Alcyon II</a> forced to rule Empire since hes the only male born while sister rules from behind<br>Winning the war, Cellesela take the throne as their house are illegemate heir of Croton<br>not only loyal people was upset for action of the nobility, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Factions/The Ori" data-href="Factions/The Ori" href="factions\the-ori.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Ori Priest</a> angered by the action, sure the Emperor have forgiven a traitor of the realm but his good outweigh the weak.<br>Wensbane find out what happened after he released, upset and heavily sad he worked with Elf who are defending themself from the cultist army, realizing losing the battle with primitive elf and Crazy Tribes Elder, he leaves to find better partner]]></description><link>remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-4-wave-of-changes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/publish/Story/Chapter 4 - Wave of Changes.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 14:15:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[An Extendable Obsidian Publish alternative using Next.JS]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a data-href="- Prologue - World Of Continenta" href="remote-blog\publish\story\-prologue-world-of-continenta.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">- Prologue - World Of Continenta</a><br><a data-href="Chapter 1 - Start of the Rift" href="remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-1-start-of-the-rift.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chapter 1 - Start of the Rift</a><br><a data-href="Chapter 2 - The Cellesella" href="remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-2-the-cellesella.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chapter 2 - The Cellesella</a><br><a data-href="Chapter 3 - The Cost of Immortality" href="remote-blog\publish\story\chapter-3-the-cost-of-immortality.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chapter 3 - The Cost of Immortality</a>]]></description><link>remote-blog\publish\home.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/publish/home.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 04:52:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[linked-blog-starter-md]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>These are the markdown files for the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/matthewwong525/linked-blog-starter" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://github.com/matthewwong525/linked-blog-starter" target="_blank">linked-blog-starter</a> repository]]></description><link>remote-blog\readme.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/README.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 04:01:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ch.1 Seas People]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>As the sun rises,<br>
The inhabitants of the land<br>
Saw their seas filled with ships of other origins.<br>
It came with peace, bearing gifts.<br>
The inhabitants called them Styria,<br>
In their tongue, as sea people. (1)<br>Their kind is weird to unwind.<br>
They leave their excess on the ground,<br>
Filthying the land.<br>
Yet their crops and kind multiplied.<br>
Heqtia always odd with her criteria,<br>
First the ashland, now the Styria. (2)<br> As the new year has come to pass,<br>
Their manner of speech became common.<br>
We started to hear their sermons,<br>
And the old inhabitants called them demons. (3)<br>Begun the first crusade.<br>
Second, we behead the renegade.<br>
Third, we drive them inland, follows cascade.<br>
Out of the fertile land, we persuade.<br>
And regain the seas that they degrade.<br>
Till we realize our heresy, taints our blade. (4)<br> Heqtia liked the Styria.<br>
While faithful novice is in euphoria,<br>
Heqtia is in hysteria.<br>
Talks of the loved ones,<br>
Leaves her as bones.<br>
And fertile land turned back withers.<br>
Here comes the never-ending winters. (5)]]></description><link>tales-of-sakkan\ch.1-seas-people.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Tales of Sakkan/Ch.1 Seas People.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ch.2 Refugee]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br> Styria’s refugees left the elderly,<br>
Lost their mother and her baby.<br>
They have tasted salty tears,<br>
Weakened with each passing year.<br>
All that’s left is closed doors<br>
From their own former neighbors. (1)<br>
Some resort to cannibalism,<br>
Few have started to perish.<br>
Left to their own devices,<br>
To escape continuous vices,<br>
Styria hides in the extremest province,<br>
Foraging nourishment from the bark of elder trees. (2)<br>
Far from the nearest main river<br>
Underground water they discover<br>
While the wood from trees inadequate<br>
Granite and minerals they aggregate<br>
After visiting the New World<br>
Finally established a stronghold (3)]]></description><link>tales-of-sakkan\ch.2-refugee.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Tales of Sakkan/Ch.2 Refugee.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ch.6 The Immortals]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Sakkan is his name<br>
Land of Lineria from whence he came<br>
Of whisper of Styria kings and queens to be,<br>
heir not born, but made (1)<br>Met folks in heaven lands:<br>
The first, is a common shopkeepers<br>
The other, a minor nobles<br>
All submit to the Styria Reverends,<br>
Whoever's child they choose to commend (2)<br>He talk to one of the shopkeepers,<br>
and she said she had both child taken from her,<br>
though she missed them both dearly,<br>
She seems to be happy knowing they're in "god's" company. (3)<br>The child could be raised as royalty,<br>
While other mothers would plead—where else could home be?<br>
Would they, too, question her loyalty?<br>
She was taken as an example, all as it was meant to be.<br>
The shop now lies quiet, the wind still.<br>
Who else could question God's will? (4)]]></description><link>tales-of-sakkan\ch.6-the-immortals.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Tales of Sakkan/Ch.6 The Immortals.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 08:38:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ch.13 Ares]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>"Little lamb yearn<br>
For its man's return<br>
Its little heart sunder<br>
Starvation comes after<br>
The lamb does not prepare<br>
Even when he's aware<br>
Lambkind comes free<br>
In the vast prairie" (9)]]></description><link>tales-of-sakkan\ch.13-ares.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Tales of Sakkan/Ch.13 Ares.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 01:08:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Timeline]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>(8 Years)(29 Years)<br>
<br>Styx-Lineria War (8 Years
<br>Reformative Era (29 Years)
<br>First Styx-Malazaer War (24 Years)
<br>Second Styx-Malazaer War (15 Years)
<br>Third Styx-Malazaer War (7 Years)
<br>

	Styx-Lineria War (8 Years)


<br>
	Reformative Era (29 Years)]]></description><link>timeline.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Timeline.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 13:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>